Can everyone see that?
[hushed chatter]
Okay, so what you don't wanna do here
is you do not wanna cut
the underlying organs,
so you are going to lift
the umbilical cord as you cut.
So now that you have the skin flaps there,
you're gonna wanna pin them down
with your dissecting pins,
which I'm clearly out of at the moment.
Okay, pin those flaps. I'll be right back.
[indistinct chatter]
[Sam chuckles]
[door closes]
[mimics oinking]
[girl 1 laughs]
[oinks to the tune of "Jinge Bells"]
-[continues oinking melody]
-[class laughs]
[class oohs]
-[girl 2] No! Ew.
-[chuckling]
-[class laughing]
-[continued oinking]
[pig whacks table]
[oohs]
-[door opens]
-[teacher] Sam.
[oinking continues]
-Sam!
-[ominous instrumentals]
Sam.
Come on...
[door closes]
[Rendell] Have a seat.
[chair scrapes floor]
"Jingle Bells," huh?
Um... Well,
Principal Westmore wants three weeks
of after-school detention.
Three weeks?
Your last incident
wasn't even a week ago, Sam.
You're...
lucky it's not worse.
People were laughing
and I guess I got carried away.
I'm sorry, Mr. Locke.
Bud, you're not the first person
to seek the approval of others.
It happens.
But lately, it feels like
you're getting carried away a lot.
What's going on?
I don't know.
How are things at home?
[deep breath] Not the best,
but I dunno. It's okay.
Look...
[deep breath] Sam... [slow exhale]
I have been in your shoes.
I screwed up a lot
in the past.
I know what it's like,
and I wanna help you.
You do?
Yeah.
You mentioned trying for vocational school
after graduation.
I did a little digging.
[Dodge whispers] Sam!
[Rendell] And I found a few programs at...
-[Dodge whispers] Sam!
-[Rendell continues indistinctly]
[Dodge] I see you, Sam.
[Rendell] How's that sound?
What's that place?
[Rendell] Uh...
That's my family's home in Massachusetts.
[Sam] It's cool.
You grew up in that house?
[Rendell] It's been in the family
for a very long time.
This etching...
it reminds me where I came from.
Helps me appreciate where I am.
[suspenseful instrumentals]
[dubious instrumentals]
[crickets chirping]
[lively instrumentals]
[song intensifies, then fades to silence]
[glass shatters]
[crunching and shattering]
[eerie instrumentals]
[takes breath]
[Kinsey] Sally.
I totally forgot about this.
I'm worried about what the Well Lady said.
I think we should call Tyler.
I lost my phone down in the caves.
The sea caves?
Yeah, me and some friends
were trying to shoot some stuff
for our film.
[peels banana]
[phone screen clicks on]
[keyboard clacking]
[phone screen clicks off]
[staircase creaks]
[pictures rustling]
[ominous instrumentals]
[floorboards creak]
[Nina exhales]
[light clicks on]
[door creaks closed]
[hangers scrape]
[zipping]
[Nina] Kinsey?
Tyler?
[distant footsteps]
All right,
I think this is the last of my stuff.
We should get Mom's phone
to check on Tyler and see if he's safe.
Okay. If you're that worried.
[crickets chirping]
[Kinsey] Shit.
Why would Well Lady break a window?
She can come and go
from any door in the house.
[suspenseful instrumentals continue]
[Bode] Maybe it's not Well Lady.
[Kinsey] Then who is it?
[instrumentals intensify]
[Nina] Tyler?
[gasps]
-[breathes heavily]
-Hey there, Mrs. Locke.
I'd really appreciate it
if you didn't scream.
-[Nina] Please don't hurt us.
-[Sam] Shut your mouth.
I want you to go hide.
What are you gonna do?
I can't just leave Mom.
I've got a better idea.
[Bode exhales]
Just don't freak out
when you see my body, okay?
What happens to your body?
I don't know. It just kinda looks weird.
Like what?
Like a sock without a foot in it.
Or like I'm dead.
Just guard my body, okay?
And keep the door open.
[key rattles and clicks in lock]
[twinkling]
-[Bode thuds]
-[whoosh]
Bode? [breathes heavily]
Holy crap!
[rushing through air]
[instrumentals soften]
[exhales]
[hushed] Okay...
[whoosh]
[exhales in awe]
Mom?
[Nina] I really don't know
what you're talking about.
-[whoosh]
-[Sam] Where are they?
-[Bode gasps]
-How did you get out?
-I escaped.
-[Bode yells] Hey!
There was a small fire.
-Then a friend helped me get here.
-[yelling] Mom!
Why did you come here?
To get the Head Key.
I'm sorry?
The Head Key?
One of the special keys.
Don't act like you don't know.
Does this have something to do
with Rendell?
Don't lie to me!
I'm not lying about anything.
[stammers] I want to help you.
I just don't know
what you're talking about.
The kids will know. Where are they?
Sam. Please, Sam.
They won't know anything about anything--
Shut up.
-[Sam] Let's go.
-Mom!
I'm gonna go get help.
[twinkling]
Are you okay?
-It's Sam Lesser.
-What?
He's got Mom... and a gun,
and he says he wants the Head Key.
-How does he know about the Head Key?
-I don't know, but he's here.
[tearing]
[Bode] What are you doing?
Improvising.
Let's go.
[Nina gasps]
Hey, Kinsey. Hey, Bode.
Let her go.
Yeah, totally. I can do that.
We can all be friends.
Just give me the Head Key.
What's that?
[gun clicks]
Do you know how angry it makes me
to be disrespected?
I know you know what I'm talking about.
So tell me where the goddamn key is
or I'm making it two for two
for dead parents.
Okay!
Just stop!
[Nina exhales]
What a bright boy.
Bode, don't!
It's okay!
I have this key.
What is that?
Where did it come from?
And it is in my possession.
Therefore,
you cannot take...
it.
This isn't how she said
it's supposed to look.
What do you mean, she?
Did Well Lady send you?
Well Lady?
What's he talking about?
You two, you know?
Yeah, but it's hard to explain.
You got what you want.
The Head Key.
Try it.
I don't think so.
[Nina stammers]
-[Nina gasps]
-[gun clicks]
What do you have?
[Nina breathes heavily]
[pats Kinsey]
You can tell
I'm losing my patience, right?
Where is the Head Key?
[shallow breaths]
Tyler has it.
Well, then...
I guess we're gonna have to wait
for Tyler.
Who's hungry? 'Cause I am.
[Tyler] What did you say
this game is called?
-["Light it Up" by ZHU plays]
-You drink, I drink.
-[Tyler] Mm...
-[liquid sloshes]
It's just so complicated.
Can you walk me through it again?
♪ You know your body is a temple ♪
[heavy breathing]
[song fades]
-[Bode struggles]
-[tense instrumentals]
Why are you wearing Tyler's clothes?
Someone has to explain to me
-what's going on.
-No, they don't.
[microwaves beeps]
Turkey tetrazzini time for all of you.
It's pretty good.
[Nina] I just...
wanna try and help you, Sam.
That's all.
-Help you get what you need.
-[food smacks in bowl]
[utensils clink]
Just spoons. No sharp forks.
[dishes clank]
I'm a vegetarian.
Then eat around the meat.
In the meantime,
I think we all ought to have
a proper catch-up...
Nobody? Okay, me first.
-[gun thuds]
-[Nina gasps]
Prison sucks, you guys.
I think that's kinda the point.
That's true.
Probably is the point.
But I broke out.
Yeah, we can see that.
How about you guys?
Come on, how's Matheson?
-How's the brain swelling?
-Kinsey!
What?
He said he wanted to catch up.
I'm just curious
how the swelling in his brain is.
You know,
from when you fractured his skull
with a hammer.
-Shame she didn't finish.
-[slams gun]
[Nina gasps]
Enough.
Eat your dinner.
[utensils clink]
[toaster clanks]
[sizzling]
One for you,
one for me.
[door opens]
[dogs bark in the distance]
What the shit is this about?
I don't remember you asking permission.
We were hungry.
And my goddamn cola?
-She was thirsty.
-[slams bottle]
-What, is there no water in the sink?
-[runs faucet]
What I thought.
-[cup clanks]
-[Sam] Hey!
"Hey," what?
Just leave her alone.
[motorcycle engine rumbles in distance]
Hit me.
-No.
-Hit me, you little wimp!
[heavy breathing]
What did I teach you?
Expect a right hand punch to be thrown,
throw your left up to block it,
and throw a right of your own.
[knocking at door]
-Where do you think you're going?
-It's my friend.
-[chuckles] Who?
-My friend.
-[dogs barking]
-Hey.
Hey.
Hey, how you doing?
I'm Randy, Sam's dad. And you are?
I'm Tyler. Tyler Locke.
-Oh, nice to meet you, Tyler.
-Nice to meet you.
You're early.
Yeah, got out of practice
sooner than I thought.
Oh, practice. What practice?
Tyler's on the hockey team. Let's go.
[birds chirping]
[Randy] See you around, Tyler.
[Tyler] Yeah, see ya.
[Randy] You fellas have fun.
[gulps]
That's an interesting tattoo, Sam.
The Omega symbol.
Came out well, I think.
I noticed it the last time we saw you.
-[tense instrumentals]
-You wanna talk about Mr. Locke?
[utensils clank]
I was asking about your tattoo.
Because you want to know
what it has to do with Mr. Locke.
-You think I'm stupid?
-I do.
Well, I'm not.
So, let's do it.
Let's talk about Mr. Locke.
What would you guys say to Rendell Locke
if he were here right now?
I'd tell him he should've had
your looney tunes ass committed
before you destroyed our family.
What would you tell him, Sam?
The man who tried his best to help you
before you shot him?
I'd tell him...
that this is all his fault
and it always has been.
Why is it his fault, Sam?
If you explain it to me,
I can help you get what you want.
Who sent you to our house
back in Seattle, Sam?
Dodge cares about me.
She's the one who needs the keys.
Well Lady's name is Dodge.
You know who he's talking about?
Why does she want the Head Key?
Because the Head Key allows you
inside someone's head.
And someone knows
how to open the black door.
Who knows?
It's none of your business.
Did this Dodge person tell you
to kill Rendell?
Remind me why
I have to answer any of your questions.
I'm the one with the gun.
[hip-hop music plays faintly on radio]
So what do we do now?
[sighs] What do you mean?
I mean the night's young
and I'm not done with you yet.
[chuckles]
I really, um...
I really should be getting home.
I know this really good bar
just outside of town, huh?
I really should go. Some other time,
-maybe.
-Okay.
-[keys jingle]
-[engine turns over]
[suspenseful instrumentals]
Okay, why don't we just
drive by the lighthouse then?
Maybe go for Round Two.
Oh, thanks.
Can you give that back, please?
What?
This key?
Give it back.
Now.
[dog barks in the distance]
Why don't you just take it from me?
-[screams]
-[gasping and panting]
[suspenseful instrumentals intensify]
[turns handle]
[heavy breathing]
-[gasping]
-[key rattles]
[breathless] Key House!
[heavy breathing]
[screams]
-[instrumentals fade]
-[Tyler pants]
[heavy breathing]
[clock ticks faintly]
[Sam] What do you have for dessert?
Hope you're not one
of those sugar-free mothers.
-[tense instrumentals]
-[Nina] There's popsicles and ice cream
in the freezer.
[Sam] In prison,
I had this caramel custard thing.
That was really good.
-[grunting and thudding]
-Get him, Ty!
[grunting and gasping]
-[Nina gasps]
-[whacking]
[struggling]
-[Nina] Tyler! Tyler, be careful!
-[Sam grunts]
[grunting and struggling]
[Sam gasps for air]
[flames roar]
[Tyler yells]
[gasping]
-[Tyler] No!
-[Nina gasps]
[heavy breathing]
Quite the greeting, Ty.
But I'm glad you're here.
I need the Head Key.
What?
[yelling] The Head Key! Now!
-I've been waiting!
-I don't have it!
[Sam] Bullshit!
[gun clicks]
Sam!
You have three chances
to give me the right answer.
-[Tyler] Sam!
-Tell him, Kinsey. Now!
Tyler doesn't have it!
Of course you lied.
-[Nina exhales]
-Where is it?
I buried it.
Out in the woods.
Why would you bury it in the woods?
Because it's dangerous!
And we knew somebody might want it.
[Tyler breathes heavily]
Why should I believe
a word you're saying right now?
Because I don't want you to hurt
anybody else in my family.
-[gun clicks]
-Well, then...
you, me and Bode
are gonna go dig it up.
-[zipping]
-[Sam grunts]
[Nina exhales sharply]
[keys rattle]
-Sam? Sam. I'll go with you.
-[Sam] You're not going anywhere.
-Take me instead.
-Shut up!
I don't need either of you.
-[Kinsey] Bode doesn't need to come.
-[clears throat] Sure he does.
He's my collateral.
[chair thuds]
Right, little buddy?
[Nina] Sam,
if you harm my children,
you will wish I only had a hammer.
-[chair thuds]
-Do you understand me?
Such a spitfire.
[chair scrapes]
That's exactly why I'm taking them
and not you.
Let's go.
[chairs scrapes]
If something happens to me,
remember to take care of Sally.
[Nina] Sam!
Please!
-[crickets chirp]
-[insects trill]
[Kinsey] So,
what happens when Dodge
or whatever opens the black door?
-[vegetation crunching under steps]
-Shut up and walk.
I bet you don't even know
why you're doing this,
-do you?
-I said be quiet!
You can't trust her.
All she does is lie to make you do stuff
you shouldn't do.
She lied to me and now she's lying to you.
-[lantern thuds]
-Spoken as the son of a liar.
So... [clicks pen]
-how have the past few weeks gone?
-[deep breath] Good.
Really good actually.
I don't know if Tyler told you,
but him and I have been hanging out some.
Well, that is, uh... [chuckles]
that is good to hear, Sam.
-And class is going okay?
-Yeah.
How are things on the home front?
-[phone rings]
-Hold that thought.
Hey.
[sharp inhale] Oh, uh...
Yeah, hold on a sec.
Yeah, tell him I'll be right there.
Okay, thanks.
-[receiver clanks]
-I'll be right back. Hang tight.
[door opens and closes]
[Dodge] Sam?
Sam?
[approaching footsteps]
-[ominous instrumentals]
-You don't have to be afraid.
What are you?
I'm your friend.
I...
Or at least I want to be.
Look on the desk, Sam.
Just look.
[picture rattles on desk]
Open it.
[pages rustling]
They're not your real friends, Sam.
They lie to you.
-[gasps]
-You're nothing more than a virus to them.
But me...
I would never lie to you, Sam.
'Cause I know how special you are.
[yelling] Stop!
This isn't real!
Yes, it is, Sam.
And I know how to get you what you want.
You just have to listen to me, okay?
Just listen.
[indistinct chatter]
[girl] Whoa...
[Rendell] Sam? [yelling, echoes] Sam!
[crickets chirp]
This is the spot.
Sit.
-[lantern thuds]
-Dig.
[suspenseful instrumentals]
[shovel thuds into ground]
[heavy breathing and struggling]
Oh, it's no use.
[Nina sighs]
[chair creaks]
-[heavy sigh] Screw this.
-What are you...
-[chair creaks and thuds]
-[Tyler grunts]
-[gasps]
-Jesus, Tyler. Are you okay?
[breathless] Yeah, I'm all right.
-[chair backs rattle]
-[Tyler grunts]
[struggling]
-You have your phone?
-Yeah.
-[snips]
-Where were Bode and Kinsey
-before Sam got here?
-Winter Study.
[dials phone]
[ringback tone]
[woman] 911, what's your emergency?
[wolf howls in the distance]
[shovel thuds]
You do know
that if there's no Head Key down there,
I'm gonna have to kill both of you.
-It's down here, I promise.
-Then hurry up!
[shovel rattles]
[blade tings]
[suspenseful instrumentals intensify]
Really?
That was your plan?
[struggling]
[knife clanks]
-[Kinsey sighs]
-[gun clicks]
I have no choice now.
You realize that, right?
[rustling]
[continued rustling]
[Sam] What?
[low groaning]
[creature screams]
[screeching]
Holy shit!
-[whacking]
-[Sam yells]
[struggling]
-Let's go!
-[Sam screams]
[suspenseful instrumentals continue]
[sighs]
[Nina exhales sharply]
-What did the cops say?
-Five to ten minutes.
-[grunts]
-Maybe we should go out there.
What are you doing?
What is that?
[shrieking and screaming]
[slashing]
-[whacking]
-[Sam struggles]
[gun shot]
-[creature whines]
-[gun shot]
[screaming]
-[distant gun shot]
-Oh, my God!
[Sam pants]
Mom! Mom, wait!
[screaming] Get out of my way!
-He shot them!
-[door opens]
[heavy breathing]
[instrumentals intensify]
Shit!
Tyler?
Enough of this.
-[Nina grunts]
-[Sam screams]
-[swipes knife]
-[Nina grunts]
[struggling]
[thud]
[Nina struggles for air]
-[gun clicks]
-[Nina exhales]
You made me do this!
I can't let her down! I can't!
[heavy breathing]
-[key crunches in opening]
-[gun thuds on floor]
[Nina pants]
What the hell is that?
-Holy shit!
-What the hell is going on?
Sam, Bode and Kinsey?
They ran off. Into the woods.
The gunshots.
Some creature attacked me.
Bode and Kinsey are okay?
If that thing didn't get them. Is that me?
And that's my front door.
[stammers] What the hell is happening?
It's the Head Key.
And this is real?
You've seen it before, Mom.
Not this, but magic.
You just can't remember.
Why can't I remember? [sharp inhale]
Is this why you killed Rendell?
Tyler, I screwed everything up.
[cries] Oh, my God.
[dramatic instrumentals]
Oh, shit.
I didn't wanna kill Mr. Locke,
I didn't.
I just wanted to find the keys for her.
Dodge?
[Sam trembles]
[stammers] That thing I said to you
about my dad, that...
had nothing to do with it?
If you ever do decide to kill your dad,
do me a favor:
kill mine while you're at it.
What did you say to me? [pants]
It doesn't matter.
[inhales sharply]
I thought you were my friend.
But you lied to me.
You and your dad, you both lied to me.
Yeah, my dad pushed me
to hang out with you to...
to try and help you!
But I actually liked you
and we were friends,
until you showed up at my house
[yelling] with a gun!
[heavy breathing]
She told me I was special.
That she cared about me.
You think if she really cared about you,
she'd be making you do any of this?
You don't understand.
No. I think I do.
-[suspenseful instrumentals]
-[truck squeaks]
What's on the other side of that door?
It's inside Sam's head.
What do you mean his head?
[Tyler] Mom.
Mom. Mom! Stop!
-[key crunches and rattles]
-[Sam gasps]
[heavy breathing]
-[whack]
-[Tyler thuds, grunts]
-[slaps]
-[Nina grunts]
-[thuds]
-[Tyler groans]
-[continued groaning]
-[gun slides across floor]
[Tyler gasps for air]
-[Dodge] Thank you, Sam. You found it.
-[Tyler] Sam!
-She can't take it from you.
-[yelling] Shut up!
Not unless you give it willingly.
All of this could've been avoided
if your idiot father
had just told Sam what I needed to know.
[dramatic instrumentals]
What are you doing?
Do you really think I'm special?
Of course I think you're special, Sam.
Promise me you're not lying.
-[Nina groans]
-Mom.
Mom, are you okay?
Do you think I would lie to you?
[police sirens in the distance]
[heavy sigh]
[Tyler] Sam.
Sam!
Just tell me you're not lying.
Just tell me!
[Nina exhales]
[knife tings and rattles]
[Sam struggles]
Maybe I can't take keys from the Lockes...
but anyone else is fair game.
Let's go.
[screaming] Let's go!
Come on! [cries out]
[key dings]
[keys rattle together]
[sirens intensify]
[breathless] Why did you?
["You're Somebody Else"
by Flora Cash plays]
[gasps] Why?
There's a reason
why no one loved you, Sam...
it's because there's nothing special
about you at all.
♪ I saw the part of you
That only when you're older ♪
♪ You will see, too ♪
Goodbye, Sam.
-[Sam cries]
-[key rattles and cranks in lock]
♪ I held the better cards ♪
♪ But every stroke of luck
Has got a bleed through ♪
[sirens wailing]
♪ You held the balance of the time
That only blindly I could read you ♪
He's inside!
-[Nina sighs heavily]
-[officer 1] I got the bags.
-♪ It's like you told me ♪
-[indistinct chatter]
-♪ Go forward slowly ♪
-[Nina exhales deeply]
♪ It's not a race to the end ♪
-♪ Well you look like yourself ♪
-[gasps]
-♪ But you're somebody else ♪
-[dispatch chatter]
♪ Only it ain't on the surface ♪
♪ Well you talk like yourself ♪
-♪ No, I hear someone else though ♪
-[door handle rattles]
-♪ Now you're making me nervous ♪
-[twinkling]
[thuds]
[distant chatter]
What the hell?
Police! Police!
♪ You were the better part ♪
♪ Of every bit of beating heart
That I had ♪
-[officer 2] We need an EMS on the scene.
-No!
[yelling] No, no, no!
♪ I finally sat alone ♪
-[indistinct dispatch chatter]
-♪ Pitch black flesh and bone ♪
♪ Couldn't believe that you were gone ♪
♪ Well you look like yourself ♪
[officer 3] We've got no vitals.
♪ But you're somebody else ♪
♪ Only it ain't on the surface ♪
♪ Well you talk like yourself ♪
♪ No, I hear someone else though ♪
♪ Now you're making me nervous ♪
Kinsey! Bode! [gasps]
♪ Well you look like yourself
But you're somebody else ♪
♪ Only it ain't on the surface ♪
[sighing]
♪ Well you talk like yourself
No, I hear someone else though ♪
♪ Now you're making me nervous ♪
[takes a deep breath]
[song fades]
[Kinsey] The cops are all gone.
[brushing surface]
Why don't we just clean up in the morning?
Bode and Tyler are upstairs?
Yeah.
Why don't you get some sleep, too?
[Kinsey sighs heavily]
I don't think
anyone's sleeping tonight, Mom.
-[Nina inhales sharply]
-[song fades back in]
♪ Well you look like yourself
But you're somebody else ♪
♪ Only it ain't on the surface ♪
♪ Well you talk like yourself
No, I hear someone else though ♪
♪ Now you're making me nervous ♪
♪ Well you look like yourself
But you're somebody else ♪
♪ Only it ain't on the surface ♪
♪ Well you talk like yourself
No, I hear someone else though ♪
♪ Now you're making me nervous ♪
[gulps]
-[taps glass]
-♪ I saw the part of you ♪
♪ That only when you're older
You will see, too ♪
♪ You will see, too ♪
[sighs]
[song fades]
[lively instrumentals]