[lively instrumentals]
[song intensifies, then fades to silence]
[indistinct chatter]
[mellow instrumentals]
-[clicks button]
-[ringback tone]
Come on, Ellie, pick up.
Hey, it's Ellie. I'm not available
right now, but if you leave your name--
[Nina] Excuse me, how much longer?
Hmm. Should be just another five minutes.
You said that five minutes ago.
Hi there.
Sorry for the waiting.
This department's not used
to handling much more
than the occasional noise complaint,
or petty theft, or van--
[exhales] Detective Daniel Matuko.
Nina Locke. I'm the one who found Joe.
-Yes, I know. I was--
-Can we talk in private?
Oh, sure. My office.
-Offer you some coffee or a fresh cruller?
-[receding footsteps]
No cruller.
Have a seat.
I'm very sorry about your friend.
I didn't know him very well,
but Joe was a beloved man in this town.
Which is why I wanted to speak to you
the other night at his house,
but they told me I had to wait.
I was actually planning
on calling you today to follow-up.
-We're still investigating Joe's death.
-It wasn't suicide.
He wouldn't do that.
Like I said,
we're still investigating Joe's--
Joe was murdered.
What would make you think that?
When I was there, the door was unlocked.
[stammers] It was open.
Most of the doors in this town
are unlocked.
I heard someone in the house.
Did you see anyone?
Any evidence
that says somebody else was there?
Well, no, no, but...
he left me a voicemail
an hour before I found him.
Hi, Nina, it's Joe.
I, uh--
[sighs] I just saw something.
But I can't explain it.
I think I just need to show you,
I'll be home all night.
-[beep]
-What do you think
-he planned on showing you?
-I have no idea.
But that's not the message someone leaves
who's about to kill themselves.
Joe had absolutely no reason
to commit suicide.
I saw him that night.
He wasn't upset about anything.
If anything, I was the one who was upset.
About what?
You might've heard that I... [sighs]
I lost my husband recently
and Joe was helping me...
try to make sense of it.
Listen...
I don't want to sound dismissive,
but I've got to go with the evidence.
And the evidence
strongly points toward suicide.
-That said,
-[heavy sigh]
we will take everything
under consideration.
What about Ellie Whedon?
Have you talked to her?
Sorry, Mrs. Locke,
I can't give you any more details.
Is this Joe's?
Yeah, we found that
on his desk
in his home office.
He said he had to show me something.
-It could've been something in this box.
-I'm afraid I can't let you do that.
But you have my word, I will be in touch
as soon as I know more.
[Nina sighs]
[receding footsteps]
[Duncan] Rendell, no!
[whacking]
[key tings]
[key rattles]
So crazy, right?
We just saw him
and now he's gone.
[mellow instrumentals]
[Tyler] You never know
what's going on in someone's brain.
That's true.
Hey... do you still wanna come over later?
Yeah, of course.
Okay.
[Scot] Okay, so we have a big problem.
-The climactic demise of Nephropidae.
-[door closes]
The first cut came out a bit rubbish.
What, don't think we cracked the lobster?
-[laughing]
-[Scot] Good one.
But it's not all bad news, however.
-I found another solution.
-And by "I," you mean--
[Scot] We, sorry.
None of this would've been possible
without the brilliant Kinsey Locke.
I'm sorry, none of what, exactly?
Oh, I've written a few extra scenes
that I really think
will make this thing sing,
and Kinsey and I have already shot one.
[birds chirping]
And how's that?
All the equipment's in my van.
[stammers] Well, we...
Kinsey had a work around.
-[phone chimes]
-[Douglas] Shit.
What is it?
[sighs] We lost the Matheson Docks.
-As in they... they sunk?
-[Douglas] As in Mr. Peña,
the owner,
won't let us film there.
Why not?
He doesn't wanna deal
with potential liability... Blah, blah.
See, there's a reason
no one wants to shoot in Matheson.
This town is so not ready
for it's big break.
[groans] Okay, it's fine. It's okay.
We will find something else, all right?
We have to, okay?
This is the pivotal scene.
This is our hero's epic showdown
with Nephropidae inside his lair, okay?
Let's think on it and regroup tomorrow,
all right?
[bag thuds]
[birds chirp]
[sharp exhale]
[items rattling]
[dramatic instrumentals]
[zipping]
[clanking]
[whirring]
-[light scratching]
-[approaching footsteps]
-[light clanking]
-Hey, Kins! Where's Tyler?
He's hanging at his girlfriend's tonight.
[scoffs] Gone for a few weeks
and I miss all the hot goss.
Whatcha got there?
I want to show you something.
Does it bother you that you don't remember
pieces of your childhood?
[clicks tongue]
I don't really think about it.
I think your brain forgets old memories
to make space for new ones.
What do you want to show me?
[rustling and zipping]
-[items clank]
-[whirring]
What are those?
They're memories.
I think they're your memories.
Well, how did they make...
Who made these?
I know this won't make any sense, but...
I think someone took them
out of your head.
[opens lid]
[twinkles]
I wanted you to look at them
to see if you remember
anything about them.
Duncan?
What is it? What do you see?
[breathes heavily]
Feels so familiar, but I...
I don't know what I'm looking at.
-[rushing effect]
-[sharply exhales and groans]
[sighs] Oh, I feel really queasy.
[continued sighing]
I'm sorry. This was a bad idea.
-[clanking and zipping]
-What was a bad idea?
[Nina] Dunc?
Can you give me a hand with dinner?
Yeah, I'll be right there.
Excuse me.
-[Duncan clears throat]
-[dubious instrumentals]
[pop music plays faintly through speakers]
[fire crackles]
Hey.
You good?
Yeah.
You've been staring at that same photo
of a coelacanth
for an hour and I'm just wondering
if I should be jealous.
Just... something on my mind.
Like what?
[whacks book shut]
What I would rather be doing
instead of homework.
[kissing]
[key clinks and rattles]
I didn't realize
you were rocking some bling
under there.
-Sort of.
-I didn't mean to embarrass you.
No, no, you didn't. Um...
I just...
I should get going, actually.
Sorry, did I do something wrong?
Oh, no, not at all.
I just, uh... lost track of the time.
-You're sure?
-Yeah, of course.
[zipping and rustling]
Okay, but you'll be there Sunday, right?
Set-up's at two.
Yeah, definitely.
[kisses]
-[door squeaks open]
-[descending footsteps]
[door closes]
I have to show you something.
Can't it wait?
No, it really can't.
[ascending footsteps]
I tried talking to Duncan
about what happened with Dad.
I even tried showing him his memories,
but it didn't work.
[crickets chirp]
Adults can't remember magic.
We already know this.
And by the way, you shouldn't be
doing that shit
without us talking first.
But it wasn't like
what happened with Mom, though.
Even while he was watching the memory,
it was like,
his brain couldn't process it
or something.
My brain can barely process it.
But there was one memory
he totally fixated on.
-[bag hums]
-[items clank]
-[jar twinkles]
-[Tyler takes a deep breath]
-[waves rushing]
-[seagulls caw]
[indistinct chatter]
What am I looking at?
[Kinsey] That's Dad and his friends
going down into the caves.
[curious instrumentals]
Look at this next part.
-[low humming]
-See that blue light?
Something happened to Dad and his friends
in that sea cave.
I want to go down there.
By yourself,
to chase after some weird blue light?
I'm not gonna go by myself.
[lid clanks]
I'm asking you to come with me.
No.
We don't know
what we saw in that memory, Tyler.
We don't know what Dad did!
Sure seems like he killed his friend.
It was a moment.
We don't know
what happened before.
Or after!
If we go down to the caves,
-maybe we can get some answers.
-Kinsey, stop.
-Our Dad's not a murderer!
-[yelling] Kinsey!
[breathes heavily]
I'm done with this.
-Meaning what?
-It means...
[stammers] I'm done.
I'm done with Dad,
I'm done with these evil keys!
[key thuds and rattles]
They're all yours.
[birds chirping]
[solemn instrumentals]
[hushed chatter]
Why are you avoiding me?
Nina, this isn't the time or the place.
You should've picked up one of my calls.
You're hiding something.
Outside, now.
What do you want from me, Nina?
You and Rendell have the exact same scar.
I know you didn't get it
from a bike accident.
That's what this is about?
How'd you get it?
[Ellie scoffs]
We did it to ourselves,
okay?
Me, Rendell, Mark and Erin...
senior year after our friends died,
we pressed a hot poker to our chests.
It was a way to remember them.
Well, why wouldn't you have just
told me that when I asked?
Because it was none of your business,
that's why!
[stammers, sighs] It was a private,
intimate thing.
-Now, if you'll excuse me.
-The night Joe died, where were you?
[scoffs]
[stammers] I was home.
No, you weren't.
I went to your house and talked to Rufus
right before I went to Joe's.
You weren't there.
What exactly are you accusing me of, Nina?
Just say it.
Look... [stammers] I cared about Joe.
Twenty-five years, Nina,
that's how long I've known Joe.
You've been in town all of what,
a few months?
So don't talk to me about caring for Joe.
[dubious instrumentals]
I tried really hard to be your friend.
[crunching of footsteps]
-[suspenseful instrumentals]
-[squishing]
[Zadie scoffs] Wow.
[Kinsey screams on screen]
[Zadie] How the hell did you do that?
[stammers] It's a...
time lapse effect.
-[continued screaming]
-Yeah, great work, guys. It's magical.
[Douglas] I mean, yeah, it's cool,
but let me be the one
to state the obvious here,
I mean, what's Nephropidae doing
chasing Amanda through the woods?
He's a sea monster.
[sighs] We've been over this,
Douglas, okay?
He's both water and land based.
No?
Look, what we really need
to be focusing our energy on
is finding a new location
for our final showdown. Okay? Now,
there are no bad ideas.
-Go.
-We could build one.
With what budget?
We could construct miniatures
and then film it in bathtubs.
I stand corrected,
there are definitely bad ideas.
-I thought this was a safe place.
-Well, I'm sorry Douglas,
but we're making a monster piece here.
I have an idea.
What if we shoot
in the sea caves?
Uh...
[laughs] I don't think that's a good idea.
You know that they're nicknamed
the "Drowning Caves" for a reason?
It's really not that scary
as long as you're careful.
I've been down there before,
it's insanely cool!
No, it would be a bitch
to get all our equipment down there, so--
There are rumors
that place was like a government site.
What if there's radiation or something?
I don't want to grow a third arm.
You guys are being such killjoys
right now. Come on!
I actually love this idea.
[laughs] I mean,
where's your sense of adventure?
Yeah, you said yourself,
you don't want it to look like
some cheap, hacky, home-made film, right?
Well, obviously.
Okay, unless someone's got a better idea,
I vote sea caves.
[distant chatter]
All right, sea caves. Let's do it.
[floorboards squeaking]
[hushed, indistinct whispering]
[sighs]
[curious instrumentals]
[hushed whispering intensifies]
[key cranks]
[key clicks outward]
Okay...
[latch clicks]
Okay.
[key clinks in lock]
[cranking]
[click]
Perhaps this is a Narnia situation.
[door squeaks]
[serene instrumentals]
Whoa.
It looks just like our world.
Morning, kiddo.
Want some cereal? [gasps]
You found the key!
That's great.
I found that cabinet in the basement
a few weeks ago.
-There's nothing magical about it.
-Well, not yet.
Wait till I refinish it.
-[approaching footsteps]
-[Kinsey] Hey, Mom,
do we have any flashlights?
Mm...
Try the closet upstairs.
What do you need them for?
[phone chimes and buzzes]
[clicks button]
Hello?
Hi. This is Detective Mutuku.
Yes. Hi, Detective.
We found no signs of forced entry.
No robbery, no fingerprints on the bag
other than Joe's or yours.
No physical evidence
inconsistent with him killing himself.
We interviewed a number of people
that were close with him
and all of them described him
as being lonely.
[box thuds]
This upcoming weekend was the anniversary
of his wife's death.
You're ruling it a suicide?
[sighs] Yes.
Okay.
-Is that it?
-Uh.
I didn't find anything in here.
Just some photographs
from when he was a yearbook adviser.
Given that they're no longer evidence,
you're welcome to have 'em.
Thank you.
-[door opens]
-[Duncan breathes heavily]
Hey, Uncle Duncan,
do you wanna go outside
and explore?
I wish I could, bud,
but not now.
I'm sorry,
I'm still fighting this migraine.
I think
I'm almost on the other side of it.
I'm gonna have to take a raincheck, okay?
Okay. [heavy sigh]
-I'll be outside. Hope you feel better.
-Mm-hmm.
-[birds cawing]
-[wind blowing]
[whoosh]
[suspenseful instrumentals]
[sharp crescendo]
Hello, Bode.
What do you want?
I'm going to give you one last chance
to give me the keys.
Never.
And I know you can't take them from us.
You have no idea what's coming.
[ominous instrumentals]
It's gonna destroy your family
and you'll be the one responsible.
Don't say I didn't warn you.
-["Brown Paper Bag" by Yoshi Flower plays]
-♪ Breathe in, breathe out ♪
♪ My daily meditation ♪
♪ Breathe in, breathe out ♪
♪ Help me when I'm escapin' ♪
♪ You're keeping me from fainting ♪
♪ Breathe in, breathe out ♪
[sparks hiss]
[door piece thuds and rattles]
♪ Know your love's gonna last
Even if I was hopeless ♪
[door squeaks open]
♪ Rob and steal ♪
♪ Everything you conceal ♪
♪ All the ghosts from my past
Get a toast and I laugh ♪
♪ As I choke on this gas ♪
♪ Oh, yeah, yeah ♪
[flames roar]
♪ Breathe in, breathe out ♪
-What the hell happened?
-I dunno, whole block's on fire.
[officer grunts]
[officer groans]
[officer screams in agony]
[distant police sirens]
-[song stops abruptly]
-[phone chimes]
[birds chirp]
[mellow instrumentals]
[keyboard clacking]
[phone whistles]
[Duncan] Hey, I'm taking off.
My headache's finally eased up, so...
What is all this?
I'm looking for something.
[Duncan] Can I help?
I don't even know what I'm looking for.
but... I'm not crazy.
Who said you were?
Ellie. I think messed things up with her.
I accused her of something,
and I don't know.
Maybe she was telling me the truth.
-Truth about what?
-I wanted to know about this scar she has.
It's the exact same scar that Rendell had.
Do you remember that?
Right here, by his collarbone?
[birds chirping]
Not really.
Another thing you don't remember?
-[exhales]
-I don't know,
maybe the answer's not in this box.
I just know...
that something feels off here.
I think you need a good night's sleep.
-[chuckles]
-I'm sure that's true.
Why don't we round up the kids,
I'll drive us
back to Boston tonight,
Bryan and I will take the kids out,
and you can just rest.
Thanks.
But, you know, I'm okay here.
[Duncan] Okay.
Talk in the morning. Hmm?
[Nina] Sure.
-[dramatic instrumentals]
-[waves crash on shore]
[water dripping]
-[Kinsey gasps] No way.
-[laughing]
[Scot] Man, it really does feel like
some otherworldly creature
could be lurking here, huh?
[laughs]
Exactly. Come on!
[Zadie] Now, this is cool. I mean,
kinda scary, but really cool. [laughs]
Pretty awesome, right?
-Yeah, it's amazing.
-[Zadie] Yeah.
Yeah, the Matheson Docks are just like,
a super embarrassing memory right now.
[laughing]
[Scot, distant] All right,
what if we put the camera here?
We can catch the shot
of this dramatic entrance.
[Douglas, distant] That's perfect!
Plus we get all this nice lighting
in the back side.
-[Zadie] Shall we set up?
-[Scot] Yeah.
[hushed, indistinct whispers]
[Scot] Kinsey, you got the tripod?
Kinsey? Kinsey?
-[waves crashing]
-I think we should keep going.
[Scot] What? No, no, no, no.
This place is perfect!
No!
-There's a better location further in.
-[Douglas] Yeah, I don't know about that.
That tunnel looks a little...
hard on the ankles. And it's wet.
Yeah, and we'd have to bring
all this equipment down there.
Yeah guys, seriously, I...
I don't want anybody to get hurt,
and I don't think
I have phone signal here.
Look, I'm telling you it's safe.
And it's gonna be totally worth it.
Trust me.
Sounds like she knows
what she's talking about, guys.
For Nephropidae, right?
[tripod clatters]
[bag thuds]
[water splashes]
-Kinsey, just wait a sec.
-[water spraying]
[feet whack surface]
After you.
Never question my commitment
to my craft ever again.
[laughs] I only said that
because you were the one
who insisted on shooting
-from your dad's freaking La-Z-Boy.
-It was the best angle,
okay?
-[Zadie] Really?
-Yes.
[Douglas groans]
-Oh! Take the head.
-[Scot] Guys.
[distant yelling]
[Scot] Yo, guys.
-[heavy breathing]
-[tripod clatters]
[Kinsey] Here.
[Gabe] Hey, wait up, huh?
[Gabe exhales and grunts]
[wind rushing]
-[water splashes]
-[Kinsey exhales]
[hushed, indistinct whispering]
[dubious instrumentals]
[Gabe] Holy shit.
-[Zadie] Oh, my God.
-[Douglas] Whoa!
[laughing]
[Douglas] Yeah, okay.
Yeah, you were right, Kinsey.
[Zadie] Wow, Doug gave his approval.
This, my friends, is a miracle cave.
Told you guys.
[Gabe] I can see Nephropidae crawling out
-from, like, right over there.
-[Zadie] Oh, I love it.
What do you think, Scot?
Scot?
Oh, sorry, I was...
just practicing my Oscar speech
-in my head.
-[laughing]
[Scot] All right, let's do it. Get set up.
[indistinct chatter]
[breathes heavily]
[indistinct whispering intensifies]
[formidable instrumentals]
[omega whirs and hums]
[whispering intensifies]
I could get used to having a lair.
[Zadie exhales]
-[water splashes]
-What the...
[stammers] I don't understand how...
[water sloshing]
Uh, guys?
What is happening here?
[suspenseful instrumentals]
Oh, shit.
I think the tide's coming in.
We're already in so far.
How can it get all the way in here?
Well, it's the ocean, Doug.
It's pretty bloody agile, yeah?
Pack up everything, we're leaving now.
[Scot] Oh, man, this really isn't good.
Where's Kinsey? Kinsey!
I'm gonna go get her.
I'll get her. You guys go.
-No, we'll wait!
-No, that's putting everyone else
in danger. Get out of here!
I'll meet you.
[Gabe] Kinsey!
-[Douglas] He'll be fine.
-[Gabe] Kinsey!
[whirring and humming]
[breathes heavily]
-[door rattles]
-[Kinsey sighs]
-[water dripping]
-[gasps for air and coughs]
We can't wait, we have to go now!
-What about our equipment?
-Leave the stuff--
We have to swim. It's flooded all the way
to the other cavern. Yo, let's go!
No, no, no,
I don't think I can do that, okay?
-Maybe if we just climb high enough--
-There is no high enough, Doug, okay?
This thing is filling up
and it's filling fast. Okay?
If we don't go now,
I promise you we will drown.
Okay, now me and Zadie will help you.
Let's go.
[suspenseful instrumentals]
[yelling] Leave your bloody shoes, Doug!
Let's go!
[Gabe] Kinsey! Kinsey, come on,
we have to go.
The caves are flooding.
Kinsey, we have to go.
-What are you doing?
-Get off me!
[heavy breathing]
-Okay.
-[Scot] Nice and steady.
Oh, my God. It's cold!
-[water sloshing]
-It's really cold!
We've got to swim to the other cavern.
It's coming up.
-[gasps for air]
-Here it is. All right.
Okay.
On three, okay? Just take a deep breath
and don't stop swimming.
One, two, three.
Oh, God! Oh, God! Oh, God! [gasps for air]
[heavy breathing] Okay...
-[gasps for air]
-[Gabe] Kinsey, the cave is flooding!
If we don't go right now,
we're both gonna die. Come on, please.
[heavy breathing]
Kinsey, let's go.
Come on.
[low vibrations]
[suspenseful instrumentals continue]
-[feet shuffling]
-[heavy breathing]
[Kinsey] Oh, shit.
[Gabe] I told you.
We can do this.
[Kinsey] My flashlight's waterproof.
I'll go first.
[pants]
[gasping and coughing]
Oh, my God, I made it.
-I can't believe I made it.
-What about Gabe and Kinsey?
[panting]
[water sloshing]
[gasps for air]
[bubbling]
[gasping and coughing]
-[Gabe] You okay? [coughs]
-Yeah, just a little farther.
-[Gabe] I don't think we're gonna make it.
-Yes, we are.
[sharp inhale]
-[Scot] Kinsey!
-[Kinsey coughs]
[Kinsey pants and gasps]
[Douglas] That was fun.
-Why didn't you tell us that could happen?
-I didn't know!
Even though you're such an expert
on the caves?
[yelling] We could've all died!
I know, I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry, but at least we're all safe.
We lost all our gear!
-So? We'll replace it! I'll replace it!
-With what money?
Kinsey, do you know how many hours
of scooping ice cream
it took me to buy all that stuff?
You said you wanted a good location,
so I...
-Oh, bullshit! You left us down there!
-...was just trying to help.
Did you even care about this film at all?
Why are we even here?
I have more to worry about
than this stupid little movie, okay?
[water sprays]
[heavy sighs]
[somber instrumentals]
I never should have trusted you.
Never.
[inhales sharply]
[waves crash]
[takes a deep breath and exhales slowly]
You saved my life back there.
You know that, right?
I would've drowned.
Well,  I'm sure you would've done
the same thing for me.
Besides, I can't really blame you.
I mean, that door was... [scoffs]
What the hell was that thing?
I don't know.
I think it has something to do
with the magic,
and the keys.
What, you might have a key that opens it?
No.
I... don't really have anything.
I don't even have the Savinis anymore.
Just... give them some time,
they'll get over it.
[scoffs] Sure.
I should never have made you guys
go down there.
[sighs] You didn't make us do anything.
No, I did.
I lied about knowing about the cave.
Well, I, for one, am glad we did it.
I'm serious.
What else would I have been doing today?
Filming some crappy little scene
in Doug's basement? Doing homework?
I mean, I'm excited to be alive right now!
And not just because we almost drowned,
but you just... [takes a breath]
you have that effect on people.
You have this energy that I think
we'd all follow, anywhere.
I mean, I would.
[birds chirping]
You're a badass.
[Kinsey scoffs]
I don't feel like a badass.
I like this Kinsey.
[dramatic instrumentals]
[kisses]
-["Glo Up" by LATASHÁ plays]
-♪ Still don't know how they feel ♪
-[phone buzzes]
-♪ To this day I would live on the real ♪
-[phone dings]
-[screen clicks closed]
♪ I'mma keep it trill,
I'mma keep it trill on the glo up ♪
[girl laughs]
[indistinct chatter]
♪ On the glo up ♪
[phone dings]
Hey, what are you doing here, man?
-What do you mean?
-[screen clicks closed]
Uh... the 5K is happening like right now.
[sighs] You're not there either, dude.
Jackie wasn't counting on me, dude.
She was expecting you.
I'm sure she's got it under control,
just like everything.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I thought you two were hitting it off,
-what's up?
-You know, I'm gonna get another drink.
-[sighs]
-[phone dings]
-[Javi] Hey! Lockestar!
-[laughs]
We miss having you on the team, man.
Not sure that's true,
but I miss you guys, too.
See, you're softening up all ready, bro!
Me and Javi are doing this thing
where on every third day,
we only eat meat.
Really starting to see the difference
actually, though.
[Javi laughs]
Whoa. Who is that?
♪ No speech with it ♪
♪ Still don't know how to spill ♪
-♪ To this day... ♪
-[song fades into ominous instrumentals]
So,
where can a girl get a drink around here?
[clicks tongue] Um...
You can have mine.
[song fades back in]
What is that, vodka and Kool-Aid?
What can I say? My, uh...
My body is a temple.
Yeah, I can see that.
You know, we can...
we can get you something better.
Come with me.
-["This Is Ridiculous" by Twirl plays]
-[laughing]
[indistinct chatter]
Lucky bastard.
Damn right.
Ooh, spoke too soon.
Uh, dude, Jackie Veda just showed up.
Who's Jackie Veda?
-Uh... [sighs]
-She's, um...
-Right.
I get it.
I will see you around.
I'm sorry we didn't get
to spend more time together.
-I can't believe you.
-Jackie,
-uh...
-You knew how much this mattered to me,
how much it mattered to Mr. Ridgeway.
[stammers] Trust me,
I'm doing you a favor.
Bailing on something you knew
was important to me, that's a favor?
Better sooner than later.
Look, I know you're going through a lot
right now...
[takes breath]
I just wish you would tell me.
You can't understand, you really can't.
Fine.
[cap rattles]
-[glass taps]
-Am I understanding you now?
Jackie, what are you doing?
[Jackie] Yum...
-[glass taps]
-Let's play some beer pong.
No, no, maybe we should wrestle!
Go home.
No, I'm having fun. You go.
You deserve better.
Well, at least we agree on something.
[sighs]
[crickets chirp]
[dog barks in the distance]
-[lo-fi music plays]
-[door closes]
♪ Locked out in the corner ♪
-[door squeaks open]
-Hey.
♪ Locked out in the corner ♪
How'd it go with what's-her-name?
Really great.
I can tell.
[bag rustles]
[hollow thump]
You're not gonna make me drink this alone,
are you?
♪ Conversation to set us free ♪
♪ 'Cause I need you ♪
-♪ And I think that you need me, too ♪
-[door slams]
There you are!
I'm unpacking.
You know,
I swear I had more boxes than this.
Are you okay?
Have you seen anything weird?
Are all your keys
present and accounted for?
-What's the matter with you?
-The Well Lady came back!
She did? Where?
Outside!
She said something bad is going to happen
to our whole family
and it was gonna be all my fault.
-Bad like what?
-She never told me!
[sighs] It's okay, bud.
She's just trying to scare you
into giving her what she wants.
Look, I'm not afraid of her
and you shouldn't be either.
And she can't take the keys from us.
[Bode sighs]
All right.
But I'm not leaving your side tonight.
So does that mean you'll help me
carry boxes up from the basement?
Fine.
[Kinsey laughs] Come on.
-[car engine rumbles]
-Where are you right now?
[clicks tongue] Uh...
Beautiful downtown Matheson.
No.
[liquid sloshes]
You're somewhere else.
Sorry, I just...
-sort of a... sort of a weird night.
-Mm...
You deserve a night off
from your self-loathing,
don't you think?
-Where are you from?
-[laughs]
I don't care.
You shouldn't either.
See?
How freeing it can be
when you get out of your own head?
[both laugh]
Wanna get in?
[Tyler] You sure you should be driving?
-[dog barking]
-[hushed] Who said anything about driving?
I should, uh...
I should probably get home.
Okay.
Up to you.
I don't even...
[stammers] I don't know your name.
It's Dodge.
[alternative rock music plays]
♪ You can hear them coming for you,
Coming forward to do what they do ♪
♪ You can run but you can't run far ♪
♪ I can hear them coming for you, yeah ♪
[engine hums]
-[gate rattles]
-♪ In the back with your shotgun shells ♪
♪ Now they've come to give you hell ♪
♪ No time to pack your cards ♪
♪ 'Cause I can hear them
Comin', comin', comin' ♪
[lively instrumentals]