[lively instrumentals]
[song intensifies, then fades to silence]
-[Ellie] Great work today, you guys.
-[students murmur]
Sarah, strong finish. I loved that.
[Sarah] Thanks, Ms. Whedon.
[Ellie] Alexis, did you find a ride home?
[Alexis] Yeah, my mom's coming.
[Ellie] Good. [sighs] Okay, you guys.
Don't forget to rehydrate
-and get some rest.
-[student] Bye!
[phone buzzes and chimes]
[indistinct chatter]
[clicks open phone screen]
-[engine revs]
-[car alarm chirps]
[notification chimes]
[mellow instrumentals]
[car door slams]
[exhales sharply]
[gasps]
[Ellie] Rendell Locke is dead...
-[breathes shakily] murdered.
-[man] What?
What happened?
You know what happened.
This is all my fault.
-[kicks door]
-[Ellie cries]
What are we going to do?
I know what I need to do.
[clicks off phone screen]
[clicks open door]
[whacks chest]
[screams in agony]
[rushing effect]
[explosions]
[flames whip and roar]
[mellow instrumentals fading]
[utensils clatter]
So how are things over at Key House?
It must be pretty different
now that the Lockes have moved back in.
Actually, none of them
has ever lived there before so...
[scoffs] Right. Good point.
So, not back in, just in.
The raccoons got into the trash
last night.
Otherwise, nothing unusual to report.
Good.
I mean,
I'm glad things are going smoothly.
-[knocking at door]
-Oh.
Keep eating. I'll get it. [sighs]
[door creaks open]
[mellow instrumentals]
Lucas?
Hey, Ellie.
[kisses hand]
I'm going to need your help.
[birds chirping]
[wind chimes dinging]
[keys jingle]
-[key rattles]
-[lock clicks]
[door creaks open]
Hello?
Nina?
Anybody home?
[suspenseful instrumentals]
[ladder rattles]
[instrumentals intensify]
[door opens]
Hey, take off your wet...
-[thudding footsteps]
-shoes.
[ladder creaks]
[lamp rattles]
[faint rattling]
[bag thuds onto floor]
-[slams door]
-[clicks lock]
-[bangs on door] Hello? It's me. Ellie.
-[Nina gasps]
Oh, Jesus, Ellie.
It's me.
[lock clicks]
[breathless] Oh, God.
-I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
-[exhales sharply]
Rufus left one of his guys
and he was having a total meltdown.
-[sighs]
-[stammers] I knocked, but no one was home
so I just, I used Rufus' key.
[stammering] Ellie,
you can't just walk into my house.
[chuckles nervously]
You should have called me first.
-[sighs]
-You're right.
You're right. I'm so sorry.
I think it's just when it comes to Rufus,
[stammers] I lose my head...
[Ellie] I found it, the Crown of Shadows.
-[dubious instrumentals]
-Atta girl.
And the key?
[Ellie sighs]
Ellie, where's the key?
I only found the crown.
Well, I guess
you're gonna have to go back again.
But Nina caught me today.
Oh, come on, Ellie.
Without the key
this is just a goth accessory.
A shadow's just a shape on the wall.
Why do you want it?
[Ellie stammers]
[sighs] Where do you keep disappearing to
all the time?
[clicks tongue] Aw.
Are you jealous?
-[seagull caws in the distance]
-Why won't you just answer my questions?
-[camera shutters]
-[floorboards creak]
-Shit!
-[clicks phone screen closed]
[Lucas] Did he just take my picture?
I'll go talk to him.
[Lucas] I have a better idea.
[tires crunching on pavement]
[brakes whine]
-[engine stops]
-[lights click off]
[keys jingle]
[phone keyboard clacking]
Hi, Nina. It's Joe.
[closes door] Yeah, listen, I, uh...
I just saw something
and I can't explain it.
I think I just need to show you.
I'll be home all night.
Hi, Mr. Ridgeway.
I hope you don't mind.
We let ourselves in.
Joe, just give us the cell phone
and we'll... we'll leave, all right?
[stammering] Yeah, how are you...
How did you get here?
You died 25 years ago.
Joe,
-just give us the phone.
-Not until you tell me what's going on.
It's not going to make any sense to you!
Please!
Please.
[dubious instrumentals continue]
[Ellie sighs]
[breathes shakily]
Come on, let's go.
I wish I could, but...
[bag crinkles]
as I recall, Mr. Ridgeway, you were...
always a talker.
Listen, I don't want any trouble.
[gasps] Get off! Get off!
We have the phone.
He's not going to tell anyone.
-[Mr. Ridgeway struggling]
-What are you doing? Let him go!
Oh, my God!
[screaming] No! Let him go!
-[Mr. Ridgeway gasps for air]
-[Ellie] No!
[struggling and gasping]
[screaming] No! [cries]
[instrumentals intensify, then fade]
[car brakes whine]
[engine idles]
[Ellie] Oh, my God. It's Nina.
[Lucas] Guess I'll be going.
-[Ellie] What?
-[Lucas] Bye, Ellie.
-[key rattles and cranks in lock]
-[door creaks open]
Lucas, wait!
Shit!
[suspenseful instrumentals]
[exhales sharply]
[knocking at door]
Joe?
-[breathes shakily]
-Joe, it's Nina! I got your message!
-[clicks phone screen open]
-[keyboard clacking]
[phone rings]
Joe?
Joe!
[inhales sharply] Joe! Joe! No!
[gasping]
Oh... [groans]
[stammers] My friend's dead.
He's not breathing.
-[somber instrumentals]
-There was a plastic bag over his head.
-[breathes shallowly]
-Joe! Joe! [gasps]
[water splashing]
[slow-motion, heavy breathing]
[muffled thudding]
[gasps for air]
[pants]
[sobs]
[somber instrumentals continue]
[door opens]
[breathes shakily]
[distorted, ambient instrumentals]
[clicks gun]
[Lucas] What took you so long, Ellie?
You used to be so fast
-when you were young.
-[gun shots]
-[empty chamber clicks]
-[gun rattles on ground]
-[magazine rustles]
-[dog barking in the distance]
[suspenseful instrumentals]
-[Ellie gasps]
-[groans]
[laughs menacingly]
That really hurts...
[grunts]
my pride.
-[gasps]
-Come on, Ellie, why'd you do that, huh?
-You know you can't kill an echo.
-[exhales sharply]
I'm already dead.
-You should know that more than anyone.
-[breathes heavily]
Do you know what's going to happen
if you don't help me?
I'm going to have to tear
poor Rufus' useless little head
off his skinny little body,
and I'm pretty sure you don't want that,
do you?
[screaming] Look at me!
You should be happy, Ell.
We're together again...
and we're so close to having
everything that we need.
[instrumentals intensify, then fade]
-[birds chirping]
-[mellow instrumentals]
-[whacks]
-[body thuds]
-[Tyler] So... [sighs]
-[young Lucas] No, Rendell, no!
[Tyler] Lucas and Dodge
are the same person.
[whacks]
How is that possible?
Only thing I'm sure of
is that Dodge will come for the Omega Key.
Do you think it's safe where we put it?
Might be the safest place in the house.
-[footsteps approaching]
-[Bode] Hey, guys, look.
I found the Matchstick Key
whispering to me outside.
Sam must have dropped it.
What's that?
Nothing.
-What's nothing behind your back?
-[Kinsey] Come on.
-We should get ready for school.
-Yeah, don't wanna be late.
-I want to see it!
-No, okay.
-You, get out, now.
-[groans] Stop!
Hey! The only reason why you know
about the keys
is because of me.
Because I shared them with you.
So stop shutting me out!
We're not shutting you out.
-We're--
-You're protecting me.
Yeah, I know.
But you can stop!
I've gone through everything you have.
I'm not a stupid little kid anymore.
Dad said I was very discerning for my age.
He did, huh?
Please.
Let me help.
[mellow instrumentals]
-[twinkling]
-It's okay to be upset.
[Tyler] Memories aren't always accurate.
-They can be distorted.
-[whacks]
[young Lucas] No, Rendell, no!
That's the guy
who's staying at Ellie's house.
What?
You're saying you've seen Lucas?
[dubious instrumentals]
Rufus said he was his cousin.
There's something weird about him.
I think Rufus is scared of him.
That's because he's Dodge.
They're the same person,
or demon, or whatever.
In Duncan's memory, he used a key
that could change
what he looked like.
So if Dodge has that key...
why would she use it
to make herself look
like our dad's 17-year-old
dead best friend?
[seagulls cawing]
When he died,
what did they do with Rendell's body?
Do you remember?
[Ellie] I think they had him cremated.
Why?
Because...
if they hid the Omega Key inside his head,
then it's probably still in there,
along with whatever's left of him.
You're going to go digging around
in Rendell's ashes?
No.
You are.
[instrumentals fade]
Mom?
Are you okay?
Yes.
I'm feeling much more like myself again.
[stammers] I just...
[Kinsey] What?
[Nina] I could've sworn
something happened
to that thing.
No.
It's just been sitting there.
Like always.
Huh.
I must have just dreamt about it then.
[chuckles]
I, um...
I'm so sorry, Kins.
There's no excuse
for what I put you guys through. I--
You don't have to apologize.
Not anymore.
It's good.
We're moving forward.
-[Nina takes a breath]
-[Tyler] Good to go?
Yeah.
Bye, Mom.
[curious instrumentals]
[door closes]
[bike wheels rattle]
[drops bike]
[Bode pants]
[instrumentals fade]
Bode.
-[exhales]
-What are you doing here?
I skipped school.
Are you alone?
-Yes. My mom's at work.
-[birds chirp]
What about Lucas?
[Rufus] How do you know?
[Bode] Because your enemy is my enemy too.
Only sometimes he's a lady.
When I first moved here,
she was down at the bottom of the well.
[Bode sighs]
[exhales] After she got out,
she must've changed herself into Lucas.
[Rufus exhales slowly]
That explains a lot.
I didn't know how he came back.
What is he anyway?
I'm not sure exactly,
but something bad.
He's the reason Sam killed my dad.
[suspenseful instrumentals]
[zipping] He made my mom steal this
from Key House.
I don't know what it does,
but it must be pretty important.
There's a key you need to use it,
but my mom couldn't find it.
[Bode] I think I've seen
that design before,
but I can't remember where.
[loudly] No!
He could walk in any time. [exhales]
[zips bag]
My mom made me promise
not to talk about him.
-You should go. It's not safe.
-Rufus.
[sighs] We're fellow soldiers, remember?
We can battle this out together.
How?
[inspiring instrumentals]
I'm going to find that key.
I can hear them whisper sometimes,
and then we'll use that crown
as a weapon against Dodge.
I mean, Lucas.
You've just got to trust me, okay?
["Lay Back" by CLAVVS & Bad Tuner plays]
[door squeaks open and closed]
♪ Speaking in riddles ♪
♪ Cutting the light outta my eyes
Caught in the middle ♪
♪ What did you find buried alive
Deep in the temple? ♪
♪ What did you find?
Was it a sign? ♪
♪ Was it a symbol? ♪
♪ What did you find, find? ♪
-[song cuts]
-[creature shrieks]
[Eden screams and gasps]
[loudly] Eden! What's going on?
-[closes door] Are you okay?
-No, I'm not okay, she just...
[song resumes]
[Eden inhales sharply and exhales]
Do you not have anything better to do
in your morning?
Um... What are you talking about?
God, you are so pathetic.
You and your Santorini squad.
I will tell you this once.
You do not want to mess with me, Kinsey.
♪ Send me a signal ♪
[door opens]
-[dubious instrumentals]
-[door closes]
[closes locker]
Ellie.
Ellie!
How can I help you, Kinsey?
-Cut the bullshit.
-[indistinct chatter]
I know about the keys,
and I know about Lucas.
He's staying with you.
Bode saw him when he was at your house.
Well, Bode must have been mistaken.
No, he wasn't.
Look, Kinsey, this...
[sighs] this is not appropriate.
Goodbye.
[stammers] I'm not gonna let you
lie to me anymore.
Why are you helping him?
[Ellie sighs heavily]
Because I don't have any choice.
Do you know what he's done...
to us? To my dad?
How could you ever be a part of that?
[takes a deep breath, exhales]
I am doing what I have to do
for my family.
[student yells in distance]
And if you're smart, you'll do the  same.
-[instrumentals fade]
-[doors rattle open]
[dramatic instrumentals]
[liquid sloshes]
[sighs]
[cap squeaks]
[bag rustles]
[Logan] I don't know, Eden.
You sure it wasn't the gardener
with the hunchback?
He's pretty terrifying.
Yes, I am sure. It was Kinsey,
but the 4:00 a.m.
after an all night kegger version,
and her eyes were bloodshot
and her hair was gross. [scoffs]
Ellie admitted Lucas was there.
-She said she didn't have a choice
-[engine rumbles]
and she seemed really scared.
Dodge is too powerful.
We can't go up against her by ourselves.
So what are you proposing?
[birds chirping]
We need some help.
We should tell our friends.
[woman yells in the distance]
Scot and Gabe already know too much.
No, shutting people out isn't the answer.
I mean, this is some other worldly shit
-we're up against.
-[Eden yells] Hey!
I'm not finished with you.
[Tyler] What did you do now?
-I have no idea.
-[Eden] You know,
I always thought
that you were a freak.
Maybe she found out
about the music box prank?
This is exactly why we can't tell anyone
else about the keys.
Let's just go.
You're not so scary now without your claws
and your monster makeup, are ya?
[suspenseful instrumentals]
My claws?
Seriously, you're gonna play dumb?
[creature growls]
[creature snarls]
-[creature shrieks]
-[Kinsey] Eden!
[Eden screams]
-[stick rattles]
-[creature roars]
[Eden] Get off of me!
-[Logan grunts]
-[creature shrieking]
[grunting and struggling]
-[creature snarls]
-[instrumentals fade]
[Eden gasps] What the hell?
[heavy breathing]
[tires crunch on gravel]
[mellow instrumentals]
[wind chimes dinging]
[birds trilling]
[engine rumbles]
[keys jingle]
[key rattles and clicks in lock]
Mom. What are you doing?
We're leaving town. [sighs]
It's not safe here anymore.
Lucas wants me to do something and...
[exhales slowly]
I won't do it.
-And the Locke kids are asking questions--
-I know.
[Rufus exhales shakily]
Bode came by earlier.
What did you tell him?
[takes a breath] He's going to try to find
the key to the crown.
-Do you remember what I said to you?
-I'm sorry, Mom.
-[exhales heavily]
-I know I made a promise,
but I had to.
We need reinforcements.
[feebly] I'm sorry.
-I'm sorry.
-Oh, it's okay. It's okay. [sighs]
You didn't do anything wrong.
-[dramatic instrumentals]
-It's okay.
If we run, we'll always be afraid.
I'm sick of being afraid.
If I thought there was a way
to fight back...
Come with me.
-[Rufus] He thinks I'm dumb,
-[clanking]
that I don't see...
[Rufus sighs]
but I do.
-[items rattle]
-Did you show these to Bode?
I wanted to show you first.
[instrumentals intensify, then fade]
[Tyler] Uh...
Is any of this making any sense?
[curious instrumentals]
[sighs heavily] Okay.
So your house is full of magical keys
and there's this demon chick
who wants to take them
so she can open a black door.
Mm-hmm...
Yep. And, uh...
and Ellie Whedon is helping her.
Him, under duress.
The gym teacher. Well, of course.
Now it's getting interesting.
[scoffs] This has been going on
the whole time?
Yeah, since we moved here. Yeah.
-Pretty much. [chuckles]
-[Logan] I don't know, man.
Do you have, like, some proof or...
[Tyler takes a deep breath,
exhales sharply]
[Tyler sighs]
-[flame hisses and roars]
-[Logan gasps]
[fire crackles]
[Logan] Whoa.
[thumps book closed]
Okay...
-[stammers] That's not bad.
-[Jackie] Um...
I'm going to go check on Eden.
[retreating footsteps]
[chair rolls]
[sighs] Shit.
I haven't seen those feral cats
roaming around the school for years.
Yeah, it's pretty unbelievable, isn't it?
[nurse] You poor thing.
You just rest while I run
and get some more gauze.
[door opens]
So you didn't attack me,
but something that looks
a hell of a lot like you did.
You care to explain that?
No, I really can't.
I felt that thing's breath on my face.
[Eden sighs]
It was...
[inhales, shivers]
It was like some kind of, like...
-Monster?
-Yeah, but that's insane.
I agree. It's all insane.
Look, it's a lot to get into right now,
but...
that thing...
it's my fear.
What the hell are you talking about?
It used to live inside my head.
Now it's out and it attacks
anything I'm afraid of.
You're afraid of me?
Yeah.
You're intimidating.
You're also kinda cruel to people.
Are you seriously blaming the victim
right now?
No.
This is definitely my fault.
Well, I'm kinda flattered.
[engine rumbles in the distance]
Jackie! Hey!
Slow down. [exhales]
Are you okay?
[indistinct chatter]
Not really.
Fear monsters? Demons?
-Magical keys?
-Yeah, yeah, I know.
[stammers] It's a lot to take in. Yeah.
[sighs, stammers] I'm sorry, I just...
I need a minute, okay?
Yeah. Yeah, okay. Yeah.
So I guess you told her, huh?
[continued chatter]
How'd Eden react?
Surprisingly well.
[Tyler] Uh...
I'm gonna go get some snacks for everyone.
-You want anything?
-I'm good.
[Scot] Eden okay?
-Yeah, she'll be fine.
-[Scot] Good.
Good.
I mean, she's not exactly
my favorite person in the world,
but life would be a lot less interesting
without her, right? [laughs]
So, she got attacked
by a seven pound feral cat?
-[scoffs] 'Cause that makes total sense.
-[Scot] Mm-hmm...
Okay, here's what actually happened.
I used one of the keys
to take the fear out of my head.
[Gabe sighs]
And everything was great for a while.
Then things got messed up.
I let myself get close to you...
even though we were already a thing.
I wasn't worrying about the consequences.
-[sighs] You're both amazing.
-[Gabe scoffs]
I mean, that's the problem.
I know I should choose, but...
I don't want to.
[curious instrumentals]
What if I didn't?
What if I dated you both?
-[phone buzzes]
-[Kinsey stammers]
-[Scot] So--
-Think about it.
-[continued buzzing]
-Just give me a sec.
[Scot stammers]
-Hello?
-It's Ellie. I--
I thought about what you said.
Can we meet at Key House?
[mellow instrumentals]
[engine turns off]
[car door closes]
[approaching footsteps]
[birds chirping]
[Daniel] Nina.
[church bell rings]
Detective.
-Daniel. [chuckles] Hi.
-Uh...
Are you... you going to the meeting?
-[bell ringing continues]
-[church door opens]
I, uh... I thought so, but...
[church door closes]
I don't think I'm in the right place.
Ah. Well, maybe...
-you'd like to get some coffee instead?
-[church door opens]
-[chuckles]
-[church door closes]
-Come on.
-[giggles]
-[crickets chirp]
-[dubious instrumentals]
You have to understand, I was doing
what I thought was best for my son...
but I'm done being afraid.
Lucas, the one that I knew,
was sweet
and charming.
Dodge, that was my nickname for him.
He was on the fencing team.
[laughs] It's a little cheesy,
I know, but...
Now that name means something
completely different to me.
What happened to him?
The night after graduation,
we had a sleepover here in the basement,
but Rendell wanted to go down
to the caves.
A few weeks earlier,
we had found this door down there.
Yeah, we know about it.
Your father became obsessed
with getting it open,
and we all went
because the keys had only brought
good things into our lives.
How do you remember any of it?
The keys, the magic?
We thought after you become an adult,
you forget.
We found a way to remember.
After Rendell opened the black door,
there was this bright, blue light.
Then, these...
things shot out from the other side
like... like bullets, glowing bullets.
[exhales shakily]
I saw one of them hit Lucas.
Rendell and Lucas
managed to get the door closed again
and Lucas said he was fine,
and he did seem fine.
But later... [sighs]
[Ellie sighs]
I think it's easier if I just show you.
[neck opening crinkles]
[key crunches in opening]
[whirring]
-What?
-[Ellie] Rufus and Bode,
you two stay here.
Keep watch. We won't be long.
[suspenseful instrumentals]
[rushing effect]
[mellow instrumentals]
We got back from the caves
later that night,
tried to get some sleep,
after opening the black door
and that's when it started with Lucas.
[Lucas] Just hand it over, Mark.
[Mark] Hey, shh, be quiet!
Everyone's asleep! What do you want?
[Lucas] Hand it over. I know you have it.
-[Mark] What are you talking--
-Lucas?
[Mark] What is wrong with you?
Give me the Omega Key.
Lucas, what's going on?
-He's acting crazy.
-I know you have it.
-[Mark] Dude, just calm down.
-Lucas, what are you doing? Lucas?
-[Rendell] What the hell?
-Stop!
-[young Ellie] Lucas!
-[Mark] Make him stop.
-[Mark] Lucas!
-[Lucas, yelling] Just give me
what I want!
[Erin] Stop it! What are you doing?
[young Ellie] Let him go!
What are you doing?
[Rendell] Stop!
-[Rendell] What are you doing?
-[Lucas grunts]
-[body thuds]
-[young Ellie] Kim!
[slow motion whirring]
[key dinging]
[young Ellie] Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no.
[yelling] No, no, what did you do?
[young Ellie exhales sharply]
-He's not Lucas anymore.
-[Lucas grunts]
-[Rendell] What is wrong with you?
-[Erin] Jeff?
-[cracks neck]
-[all gasp]
-[young Ellie cries out]
-[Erin] Jeff!
[Erin] Kim!
[Rendell] What are you doing?
[young Ellie gasping]
[Lucas, gruff] Your turn.
-[suspenseful instrumentals]
-[Lucas pants]
-[whacks]
-[Lucas thuds]
-No! No,
-[young Ellie cries]
-Rendell, no!
-[whacks]
-[Rendell grunts]
-[young Ellie cries out]
[gasping and heavy breathing]
[mellow instrumentals]
[hammer rattles]
[young Ellie sobs]
[young Duncan] Rendell?
[Ellie] Duncan saw what happened.
We had no choice.
We had to remove his memories...
put them some place he wouldn't find them.
The tree.
[young Ellie cries]
[Ellie] When Lucas got hit
by whatever came across
from the other side,
some kind of demon attached itself to him.
[whirring]
[seagull cawing]
[Ellie] We created a story
about how our friends had died.
It was easier
than trying to explain the truth.
No one would have believed
what really happened.
So we told everyone that we went down to
the caves and our friends drowned...
and the bodies washed out to sea
and they were battered on the rocks.
[waves crashing]
[muffled splash]
[muffled splashing]
[bubbling]
[Ellie] We divided up the remaining keys
and we made a pact
to protect them and never use them again.
Rendell took the Anywhere and Omega Keys,
-[keys rattle]
-Erin took the Head Key,
and Mark took the Matchstick Key.
Mark hid the rest in the house.
He was the most trustworthy of us all,
so it made sense that he should know
where all the keys were hidden.
That's why he killed himself,
so no one could ever get inside his head,
to protect the keys.
What about you?
What did you take?
The Identity Key and the Echo Key.
[Tyler] The Echo Key?
[Ellie] It can bring people back...
but not in the way that I thought.
[Rufus] If we can't find the key,
we should get the traps up
around the perimeter
in case he or she or whatever shows up...
The traps didn't work.
The key ring! That's it.
-[retreating footsteps]
-The key ring?
[dramatic instrumentals]
-[rustles in drawer]
-[keys jingle]
[scoffs] I knew I'd seen it before.
[breathes shakily] I tried to move on
with my life...
but I couldn't.
[stammers] I couldn't let go of Lucas.
Other people, their lives get bigger...
fuller...
I just felt like I was disappearing.
And last year, I...
I hit my breaking point...
and I came to the Well House.
[insects trilling]
[key rattles and clicks in lock]
[gate clanks and creaks open]
[dramatic instrumentals continue]
[gate creaks]
[water drips]
[echoing] Lucas Caravaggio.
[booming effect]
[Lucas, echoing] Ellie.
[Ellie gasps and sighs]
[breathless] Lucas! Is that you?
-I'm here, Ellie.
-[gasps]
Lucas!
[Ellie sighs]
[past Ellie] I promised
I wouldn't use the key...
but I just missed you so much.
Do you have any others?
[rattling]
Just this one.
I know you can't leave this place, but...
at least I can see you now.
I can leave.
If you give me the Anywhere Key.
[exhales] Rendell has it.
Then get it from him!
Hey, no, I'm...
I'm sorry.
I'm just... I'm just frustrated.
I want to get out of here
so I can be with you.
[Ellie gasps]
I want that, too, Lucas. [sniffles, sighs]
That thing wasn't an echo of Lucas.
I didn't know
that when I called out his name
I wasn't bringing him back.
I was bringing back…
the demon
that possessed him when he died.
-[Kinsey] You couldn't have known.
-[crow caws]
The Keepers, we made a pact.
I broke that pact.
This is all my fault.
[sighs]
I just thought I could have him back.
-We should go.
-[continued cawing]
-[whirring]
-[key rattles]
[inhales shakily]
[Kinsey] When Bode met Dodge,
he was a she.
She can use the Identity Key
to transform into any form
she thinks will be most useful.
So Dodge is... an echo.
How do we get rid of it?
It can't be killed by normal means,
believe me, I've tried,
but it can be trapped in the Well House.
The problem is getting it in there.
We have a way.
[Ellie gasps]
[shivers] It's the key
for the Crown of Shadows.
Whoever wears the crown
can create and control powerful shadows.
It'll do whatever they want.
[Bode] Like...
force a demon echo into a Well House?
Exactly like that.
-So where is this crown?
-It's back at my place.
I'll get it.
[Kinsey] We'll be here waiting.
-[Rufus sighs]
-[door opens]
[wind rustling trees]
[door opens]
[suspenseful instrumentals]
[Lucas] What do you got there, Ellie?
Lucas.
You've had a busy day.
Seems someone's been rummaging
through my things.
[stammers] I took the Head Key.
Why?
[Ellie] I went to Key House
and tried to find the Omega Key
in the ashes,
but it wasn't there.
The Locke kids must have found it first.
I thought I could use it on them
to see where they put it. [sighs]
And did you?
[sighs heavily] They weren't home.
-I can try again tomorrow.
-[Lucas, loudly] Ellie! Stop it!
You're embarrassing yourself.
-[tool rattles]
-[Rufus grunts]
-[lamp clanks and buzzes]
-[grunting]
-[table shatters]
-[Ellie screams] Rufus!
[gasps] Oh, my God. Rufus!
-[gasping] Rufus! Rufus!
-[Lucas] Look at that,
what you found.
-That's very helpful. Thank you, Ellie.
-[chokes]
[breathless] Let me go.
[chokes, gasps for air]
[breathes heavily] Rufus.
-[thudding on floor] Rufus, are you okay?
-[Rufus groans]
[Ellie pants] Oh, my God.
Are you okay?
-[crown tings]
-[bag thuds]
["You Should See Me In A Crown"
by Billie Eilish plays]
♪ Wearing a warning sign ♪
♪ Wait 'til the world is mine ♪
-[key clanks and clicks]
-[whirring]
♪ Visions I vandalize ♪
♪ Cold in my kingdom size ♪
♪ Fell for these ocean eyes ♪
Hello, darkness...
my old friend.
♪ You should see me in a crown ♪
[shadows shriek]
♪ I'm gonna run this nothing town ♪
♪ Watch me make 'em bow
One by one by, one ♪
♪ One by one by, one ♪
[song stops abruptly]
[lively instrumentals]