[suspenseful instrumentals]
[hushed, indistinct whispering]
[water runs]
[continued whispering]
Hello?
[whispers intensify]
[light clicks on]
[Tyler] You hear that?
[Kinsey] It's coming from the piano.
-[light clicks on]
-[Tyler] Okay...
Hold on, we...
we should think about this.
It's the whispering, just like Bode said.
-[cover rattles open]
-[whispering intensifies]
[off key strum]
You guys can hear it, too?
-What'd you find?
-Okay, shh.
Mom's still asleep.
Let me see.
I think I've seen this before somewhere.
Seen what?
Where it goes. Over here.
[chair scrapes floor]
-[chair whines]
-[Tyler] Just... stop.
[Bode sighs]
We need to get that brown box up there,
with the swirls.
I saw it when we were unpacking.
[Tyler scoffs]
[instrumentals intensify, then soften]
[faint ticking]
[key clinks and cranks]
[clicking]
[music box melody plays]
Abracadabra?
-[Bode] I think it's broken.
-[Tyler] So,
we can all hear them now.
What does that mean?
[Bode] That means we can all be
the protectors of the keys.
Well Lady can't take them from us.
I'm not alone anymore. [chuckles]
You were never alone, little man.
We haven't seen her for, like,
over two weeks.
So? In her world that could be, like,
five minutes.
She could be, like, 10,000 years old!
Yeah, okay, Bode.
-And she's still out there!
-I know.
All right, so, for safety's sake,
we should split up the keys.
Where are the other ones?
Right here.
[keys jingle]
Head Key, Mirror Key and Ghost Key.
Kinsey, you take this new music box one.
Bode, you keep the...
the Ghost Key and the Mirror Key.
-And I'm gonna take the Head Key.
-[hushed] Yeah!
Good. Always keep them with you.
And by the way, before we use the keys,
we're all talking about it first.
Enough with the orders!
We can manage ourselves.
Yeah, you're in great shape.
Just because I don't have fear
doesn't make me irrational.
So, shut your mouth, Tyler.
-[Tyler] Mm--
-Besides, it's not like you're so above
using the keys.
Didn't you use the Head Key
to try and get with Jackie? Hmm?
-Didn't you?
-[Tyler mumbles]
-All right, very funny.
-[muffled scream]
[panicked breathing]
[continued muffled screaming]
-[Tyler pants]
-Tyler...
[muffled shrieks]
-Slap yourself in the face.
-[whack]
-[muffled groans]
-[Kinsey laughs]
-Holy shit!
-[Bode] How'd you do that?
I think it's the music box.
Tyler, open your mouth.
-[gasps for air]
-[Kinsey laughs]
Hold on, let me try this.
Kinsey,
do a back flip.
[music box melody continues]
I'm the one that put the key in...
so it only does what I say.
Bode,
pick your nose.
Oh, my God. No, no.
-[Bode] Ooh...
-These things...
-These aren't toys. They're weapons.
-[sighing]
So, until we need them,
we're not gonna use them.
Why can't they be both?
[spirited instrumentals]
Come on.
I'm not alone.
There's three of us now.
[lively instrumentals]
[song intensifies, then fades to silence]
[birds chirping]
[Tyler] Morning, Mom.
-Mom?
-[toaster clanks]
Morning.
You okay?
Yeah, I just haven't been sleeping
all that well.
You know, I've had, like,
four different guys come take a look
at that stove and no one
can find anything wrong with it.
I just... don't get it.
It's probably just a fluke.
Isn't today your first day back
on the hockey team?
Actually, I'm not going back.
[crunches into apple]
Why wouldn't you be going back?
I was fourth line, Mom.
They're not gonna miss me.
But you love hockey.
Hey, can I have a piece of your toast?
Thanks, bye.
Already talked to coach about it.
-It's cool.
-Hi, Mom.
Bye, Mom.
[sighs] Don't forget,
Duncan's coming tonight for the weekend!
[door closes]
[spirited instrumentals]
[gravel crunching under tires]
Bode, you're gonna miss your bus.
What were you doing in the shed?
Nothing.
-Did you get anything to eat?
-Love you, Mom.
[Nina stammers]
Love you, too.
[eerie instrumentals]
Nathaniel! [scoffs]
I can't believe you started the movie
without me.
I hope I didn't put too much butter
on the popcorn.
[Scot laughs] No such thing.
-[curtains rattle]
-[creature growls]
[Kinsey screams on screen]
-[blood splatters]
-[creature roars]
-[continued screaming]
-Oh, my... [laughs]
I ruined it.
What? No, no, no, no, not at all.
Your performance actually
with the scream we added is wicked.
You know, my blood
turned to cottage cheese. [laughs]
-[indistinct chatter]
-It's the rest of the damn thing.
[Kinsey] Not what you were hoping for?
[Scot] Well, let's put it this way,
if I was hoping
for a used car commercial,
I'd still be cringing
at this mess. [chuckles]
-It's just a rough cut.
-Rough?
It's bloody sandpaper.
Regretting your last-minute recast,
Kavandouche?
[scoffs] Actually, no,
I was just admiring Kinsey's skill.
[Eden] Mm...
A director blinded by the wannabe
he's sleeping with, how classic.
Eden, go away.
You know, it's such a shame
that desire has nothing to do with talent.
I hate to break it to you,
but wanting to be a director
doesn't mean that you are one.
You're just a pretentious,
mediocre little fanboy,
and that's all you're ever gonna be.
Mediocre being the key word.
Leave it. It's not worth it.
[Jackie] I've got track practice,
but did you guys want to come over
after school?
-We can sort out shirts.
-Yeah, sure.
-[door opens and closes]
-[indistinct chatter]
Hey, Logan, you think you could
come up with a reason
why you, you know...
why you can't come to Jackie's later?
Wow.
If I'm not there, who'll make sure
the larges don't get mixed in
-with the extra larges?
-[laughs]
You want some alone time with her?
It's cool.
Starting to get the feeling
she wouldn't mind that either.
Did she say something?
Nah, we've just been friends
for a long time.
I can tell.
Doesn't happen with her often.
What do you mean?
You know, she's not like Eden or me.
you know.
She's picky,
and I guess she picked you.
Don't screw it up.
I won't.
[door opens]
-[indistinct chatter]
-[lockers clanking]
Hey, you're gonna have to find
another ride after school.
I'm going over to Jackie's.
What?
I'm keeping it safe.
Didn't you say to keep them with us?
I said the keys.
Sorry.
Next time why don't you come up
with a complete set of rules?
-Don't make me that guy, Kinsey.
-That's easy, then.
Don't be that guy.
[locker slams]
That was aggressive. [chuckles]
-[zipping]
-You okay?
I'm just sick of bullies.
Well, yeah, I... I... [chuckles]
I've come to accept them
as an inevitable part
of the high school food chain.
What, so you just accept
the way Eden treats you?
[stammers] I mean, it's like...
it's like air pollution.
You know, you just don't really get
a choice in the matter. [laughs]
You know, we're not powerless here.
We have certain tools at our disposal.
Tools that open doors of possibility.
-[spirited instrumentals]
-Oh!
Oh.
And...
what exactly did you have in mind?
[instrumentals fade to silence]
-Is this a new one?
-[indistinct chatter]
[Kinsey] Yep, found it last night.
-Was it... does it...
-[dishes clank]
does it make any song you want
worm its way into the mind of your enemy?
-That's an oddly specific guess.
-I'm right,
though, aren't I?
What song shall we pick?
Maybe that Chumbawamba tune.
This is better. Watch.
[key rattles and cranks]
[music box melody plays]
Eden Hawkins...
[distorted ambient acoustics]
fall on your face.
-[Eden thuds]
-[dishes clatter]
[students laugh]
[Scot and Kinsey laugh]
[continued laughter]
[dishes and utensils clink]
[chuckles] Physical comedy isn't easy,
guys.
Think I nailed it.
-[students laugh]
-[girl] Yeah, you did!
[applause and cheering]
-That was incredible. [laughs]
-[music box melody continues]
But she's not even upset.
[Gabe] No way.
[stammering] What... Wait, how...
how did you just... [laughs]
Poor boy's short circuiting.
Listen, Gabe, you didn't just see
what you think you just...
-What do you think you just saw?
-I...
[laughs] I don't know. I mean,
I think I just saw you guys...
puppeteering Eden Hawkins.
-That's pretty accurate, yeah.
-[Scot chuckles]
This is some sort of prank,
isn't it? It is!
[laughs] How'd you get Eden in on it?
Oh, no. There's no way
she'd have been able to pull that off.
She's definitely not that good
of an actress.
It's real, but you can't tell anybody.
I mean, come on, you're telling me
that you just talk into that thing
and then she--
Does whatever I say.
You just have to put the key in
and turn it.
Okay, fine. Let me try.
[key cranking]
[music box melody plays]
Eden Hawkins,
-stand up.
-[bench scrapes floor]
[Gabe laughs]
[Eden chuckles]
-[Eden gasps]
-[Gabe] Get on the table.
-[students laugh]
-[foot thuds]
-[cheering]
-What the hell?
-[Eden thuds and gasps]
-[students ooh]
[all laugh]
-[Gabe] Make a snow angel.
-[Eden breathes heavily]
-[Gabe] Sit up.
-[students ooh]
-[Gabe] Turn over.
-[Eden gasps]
[Gabe] Do the breaststroke.
-[Gabe laughs]
-[arms squeak on table]
[continued laughing]
[Eden and students gasp]
-[feet thudding on table]
-[oohs]
-[cameras shuttering]
-Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no!
[shuttering continues]
-[squirting]
-[gasps] What is happening to me?
-[drink splashes]
-[cheering]
-[Eden exhales]
-[cups rattle on table]
[Eden breathes heavily]
Holy shit! It's actually happening.
-Oh, my God.
-Funny.
-Wait, let's make her do something else.
-Here.
-[Gabe laughs]
-I think that's enough now, though, right?
-Huh?
-What?
What? No, this is incredible!
And Eden is just the empirical worst, so--
Right, agreed. Yes, she is.
But, you know,
I think we've better stop the poison.
-[students laugh]
-All right?
So let's just call it a victory
and go to class.
[all laugh]
-You're making dreams come true, and--
-Yeah, maybe, but there is a limit.
Hey, don't touch it!
Well,
I thought that this was
about getting back at her
for what she said to me.
It was.
It is.
Okay, so I'm telling you,
Kinsey, I'm good.
Leave her be.
-[chuckles] Kinsey, please.
-Hey, she's getting up and cleaned up.
It's now or never.
[music box melody continues]
This is messed up. You guys are nuts.
[Kinsey laughs]
Thank you for meeting with me.
I just wanted to check in
and see how Tyler is doing.
This morning he told me
he's quitting the hockey team.
-He's been skating since he was seven.
-Huh.
Well, could be he's gotten busy
with the fundraiser now.
Fundraiser?
Yes, 5K run.
For cancer research.
He [laughs] didn't say anything about it.
Yeah.
I've been organizing it for years now.
So, Tyler's helping me.
He and some classmates.
They've been working every day, you know,
getting donations, sponsorships.
Happy to hear that.
[heavy sigh] I just feel like he's gotten
so far away from me.
Yeah, well, it's exciting to see
how nimble-minded
teenagers' brains can be.
They don't get stuck on any one idea,
they find other interests.
But rest assured, Nina,
Tyler is doing great.
I feel like he's moving
onto a brighter place.
[phone rings and buzzes]
Oh, sorry.
[clicks button]
Hello?
Yes, this is Nina Locke.
I'm sorry, he did what?
-[door clicks open]
-[eerie instrumentals]
[Nina] I promise you're not in trouble,
okay?
But I need to know why you brought
a blacksmith hammer to school.
[Bode] For protection.
[Nina] Protection? From whom?
Who do you think's going to hurt you?
[Bode] You can't understand.
-I wish you could, but you just can't.
-[Nina] Oh...
I'll protect you, honey.
Nothing's gonna hurt you, I promise.
[indistinct chatter]
[rattling through phone]
[whoosh]
[Tyler sighs] Come on.
Would that be an eight ball app
you've got there?
Maybe.
What'd you ask it?
I'm not gonna tell you that.
[scoffs] Come on. I didn't tell anyone
you thought George Eliott was a man.
I'm really not gonna tell you.
Someone who would use
a common misunderstanding
for blackmail?
No way.
-[laughs]
-Fine.
I don't think people should trust
fortune tellers anyway.
Oh, really?
Yes.
I think fortune tellers
are for lazy people
who let the world dictate who they are.
If you want something to happen,
make it happen.
[phone dings]
-[phone screen clicks open]
-Oh, my God.
What is it?
[clamoring and laughing on video]
What the hell is she doing?
[students ooh on video]
Okay, this video already has
over 3,000 views.
Eden loves an audience,
but why would she do this?
-[phone screen clicks closed]
-Something's wrong. I gotta check on her.
-Yeah, of course.
-[stammers] I'll text you later.
[doors squeaks open]
[Nina] Hey, take off your wet...
shoes.
[tranquil instrumentals]
[commotion]
[suspenseful instrumentals]
[creaking]
[ascending footsteps]
[footsteps intensify]
[instrumentals intensify]
-[door slams]
-[lock clicks]
-[bangs on door] Hello? It's me, Ellie.
-[gasps]
[breathless] Oh, Jesus, Ellie.
-[sighs heavily]
-It's me.
-I'm sorry. I am so sorry.
-[laughs]
Rufus left one of his guys
and he was having a total meltdown.
-[sighs]
-I knocked but no one was home,
so I just... [keys jingle]
I used Rufus's key.
[stammering] Ellie,
you can't just walk into my house.
[laughs] You should've called me first.
You're right.
You're right. I'm so sorry. [scoffs]
Um... I was just, uh...
you know, when it comes to Rufus,
I think I sometimes lose my head.
It's okay. [chuckles]
[birds chirping]
[clock ticking]
What?
Your scar.
[tense instrumentals]
Sorry to stare.
How'd you get it?
[sighs] I got it as a kid. [laughs]
[stammers] I fell off my bike.
First time without training wheels
and right into a bush with jagged stems.
[laughs] That must've hurt.
Oh, it did, for sure.
[zipping]
I gotta run. I'm so sorry again.
I promise I'll give you
a heads up next time.
Bye.
[door opens and closes]
-[birds chirp]
-[Gabe] We've got a goddamn magic key!
[Kinsey] Hey, keep it quiet.
You weren't even supposed to know.
I know. I'm sorry, but, I mean, I do know
and now I feel like I've got to know more.
In my family,
we'd call this serious questions.
-Ask away.
-Okay.
Okay, serious question:
-How did you find it?
-[takes a deep breath]
Guess you could say it kinda called to me.
Mm-kay. Okay.
Um... How does it exist?
Like, how do you think it got made?
My ancestors had a sick sense of humor?
-[leaves crunching]
-[Gabe] Hmm. Or, hear me out...
-[Kinsey] Mm-hmm...
-...you're a descendant
-of a coven of witches and warlocks.
-[laughs]
-Even better.
-Yeah, I like that.
Hmm. You know, last I checked,
that Eden video had, like, 7,000 views.
-[laughs] Oh, she deserved it.
-[giggles]
I like to think of it
more like she earned it.
Okay. Yeah, I like that. [laughs]
She put in the work and this was
her lifetime achievement award.
[Kinsey laughs]
So, why did you transfer
to Matheson Academy?
Uh... I didn't. My parents moved me
from my day school in Philly.
They're...
-[clears throat] they're getting divorced.
-Oh, I'm sorry.
It is what it is.
[sighs] Yeah, you know,
my dad's always traveling and...
[bird trilling]
my mom thinks it's good for me
to go to a boarding school, so...
Translation: she gets to pretend
that she's, like, 25 again. [scoffs]
-[crow caws]
-Anyway.
For what it's worth,
I'm glad you're here.
That's worth a lot.
Thanks, Kinsey.
Oh, hey, what's up, man?
We need to talk.
[stammers] Right. Okay. Um...
Okay. Well, I guess
I'll see you tomorrow then.
Bye.
See ya.
[door rattles open]
Can you turn your anger down,
like, 90 percent?
[Tyler clicks tongue]
Give me the key.
[scoffs] Oh, my God.
Oh, I'm serious.
Bode's gonna hold onto it,
because clearly he's far more mature
than you are.
You used the key at school today
when I explicitly told you not to.
Yeah, you did "tell" me.
But I did it anyway. And guess what?
It was awesome.
One of the best decisions I've ever made.
It's just... it's not smart.
You're not my parent.
There is a crazy, evil thing out there
who wants these keys.
Yeah, but she can't take them from us.
No, but she almost burned us all alive!
Except she didn't!
Put two and two together!
If she needs us to willingly give her
the keys,
-then she can't hurt us, can she?
-No, no, you don't know that!
We don't actually know anything.
Look, I'm sorry that you're still a slave
to your own fear, but it's not my problem.
Exactly, it's mine,
because I have to keep an eye on you
every second
so that you don't get us all killed!
No, actually, you don't.
I hereby relieve you of that burden.
Go.
Live your life.
Don't ever think about me again!
-[Tyler] Jesus Christ.
-[ascending footsteps]
What's going on?
[exhales slowly] Always good to be back.
[tires on gravel]
[lighthearted instrumentals]
[paper crumbles]
-[grunts and sighs]
-[paper thuds]
[knock at door]
Hey, man.
-You drawing?
-[light scraping]
I'm mapping out the house.
Cool colors.
-Good scale.
-[scribbling]
Is this what you were working on
in math class?
I'm guessing Mom told you to talk to me.
Perceptive.
So why don't you tell me
what happened? [sighs]
Some things are more important
than doing math problems.
[laughs] Fair point.
You want to tell me
what is more important?
Mom,
Tyler, Kinsey... you.
[chuckles]
We all need to be protected.
Well, I certainly agree with that.
I want us all to be safe, too.
How can I help?
You can't understand. [sighs]
-Try me.
-[heavy exhale]
Do you remember when you were a kid?
Sure. A little, yeah.
Did you know Chamberlain?
Chamberlain?
Locke?
The old guy in the painting?
Well, no, he probably died
a hundred years ago.
Well, I talked to him,
and he told me that you and Dad
used to play around with the magic keys,
and you became ghosts
and you used to visit with him.
Do you remember that?
Wow.
Magic keys.
That sounds really, really wonderful.
Hey, look, kiddo,
tell me how I can help, okay?
[mellow instrumentals]
It's okay if you can't remember.
It's not your fault.
[Duncan sighs]
[dogs bark in the distance]
[light tapping]
Nina?
Can we talk?
-Here we go.
-Thanks.
-Of course. So...
-[birds chirping]
what's going on?
Okay, I promise I'm not crazy,
so just hear me out.
So, Rendell had this scar
right below his collar bone.
It was really unusual.
It was like, uh...
the shape
of an upside down teardrop.
He said he got it
when he burned himself camping.
Okay.
And then, today, when I saw Ellie,
I saw that she had the exact same scar
in the exact same place,
but she said she got it
in a biking accident when she was a kid.
[chuckling] I hear you.
I just don't know what you're asking me.
Well, you knew them both
when they were young.
I'm just trying to figure out
how it's possible
for two people
to have totally identical scars
from two completely different things.
And if it's not possible,
what does that mean to you?
That Ellie lied.
Or Rendell did.
Or they both did.
Whatever happened, Nina,
it's way in the past.
Then why lie about it?
I could never get Rendell
to talk about his life here.
I'm pretty sure the reason
is that something happened.
I don't know what, but...
when Sam Lesser came into our house,
he said something about Key House
to Rendell, right before he shot him.
Honestly, it's...
part of the reason I'm here.
You know...
right after Callie passed, I, um...
I struggled for a period of time.
I mean, I kept searching for something,
someone, I could blame.
At my low point, I even sued the doctor
who was just trying to help her.
And at some point, I realized that fight
was gonna kill me...
and Callie wouldn't want that.
I appreciate that,
but this wasn't cancer, Joe.
This kid killed Rendell in cold blood.
-You know, and those scars... I--
-Nina,
it's okay to lose yourself in this...
just as long
as you can find yourself again.
[mellow instrumentals]
And I'm always here.
I'll help you however I can.
I appreciate that, Joe.
I do.
-["Give You Up" by Dido plays]
-[keyboard clacking]
[Tyler] So...
[blows air] it's all just
some performance art thing?
I guess. She still won't open up about it.
Hope she's okay.
-I'm really worried about her.
-[phone chimes and clicks closed]
-[sighs]
-You're a good friend.
Wish I'd known you in Seattle.
I would've guessed
you had a lot of friends.
Thought I did,
then all our shit went down
and everyone just sort of...
disappeared on me.
That's terrible.
♪ Didn't think I would be missing you
At all ♪
At least you had your family.
-[scoffs]
-What?
You all seem really close.
It's just... [sighs] it's just like...
♪ You don't get under my skin no more ♪
it's almost like
I have to act like their dad,
and... I suck at it.
♪ So you don't have to stay now ♪
Well, that's understandable.
[fire crackles]
I mean, you're not their dad...
but you're their brother.
And you're a good one.
Mm... Not so sure.
Come on.
You're strong.
-[chuckles]
-You're kind.
♪ You couldn't wait to leave me behind ♪
And you have a good sense of who you are.
You don't know that.
♪ Nothing you say will change my mind ♪
I do.
♪ You couldn't wait to leave me behind ♪
♪ I found a way to let you go ♪
♪ So you don't have to stay now ♪
♪ A broken mind, I came close ♪
♪ But you can't rip my heart out ♪
♪ I'm giving up ♪
♪ I'll give you up ♪
♪ I found a way to let you go ♪
[phone chimes]
♪ So you don't have to stay now ♪
♪ I'm giving up ♪
-♪ I'm giving up ♪
-[phone chimes]
♪ I'll give you up ♪
-♪ I found a way to let you go ♪
-[loud tap]
♪ It's gonna rip your heart out ♪
-[song fades]
-[loud tap on window]
[curtains rattle]
-[Kinsey laughs]
-[owl hoots]
-I have a front door, you know.
-Right,
yeah, I, uh...
I kinda always wanted to do
the pebble on the window thing.
-[chuckles]
-You know, it's romantic.
You should be impressed.
It's a pretty long throw.
I am.
But don't you think you could've just
maybe replied to one of my texts instead?
Oh, yeah, no,
my phone has been dead for hours.
If I use your front door,
can I use your charger as well?
-So, I've been thinking
-[phone chimes on]
and whilst I can't condone your actions
at lunch time--
Look, if you just came here
to lecture me--
Hold on, hold on,
hold on!
I know you were acting on my behalf,
and whilst I can't condone your actions
at lunch time,
I'm certainly not one
to be censoring the world of sorcery.
So I have a proposal:
how about we use your powers
for some actual good?
Say...
making a shit movie not quite so shit?
We're not telling the rest of the Savinis,
right?
Are you referring to Gabe?
Well, he only knows about the one key.
Let's keep it that way.
Roger that. [chuckles]
Oh, wow!
Is this...
Is this you and your tribe?
No, we just collect photos
of random toddlers.
Funny. [laughs]
And how about these very tall toddlers?
-My dad and his friends.
-[chuckles]
Oh, yeah, yeah. These are who drowned
in the caves that I was telling you about.
Yeah, I saw their picture
in an old article.
It was him, him, and her.
-[mellow instrumentals]
-How can you remember that?
It was a picture pretty much
just like that one.
What did the article say?
You know, the usual.
Great kids, full of potential,
and all that.
Yeah, they'd literally just graduated,
and they were at a party and...
[stammers] And I can't believe this is now
just occurring to me,
but maybe...
-Nephropidae devoured them. [roars]
-[laughs]
[laughs] I'm kidding. I'm joking.
Everybody knows
Nephropidae only kills for sport, so...
You'd better get back before curfew.
-I'll see you soon?
-Yeah.
[swelling instrumentals]
[kisses]
[door opens and closes]
[curious instrumentals]
[knocking at door]
[dog barks in distance]
Hello, Mrs. Locke.
Hey, Rufus.
Is your mom here?
I'm not supposed to tell strangers
when I'm home alone,
but you're a friend, so...
my mom isn't here.
Please tell her to call me
as soon as possible, okay?
I can do that.
Do you want me to tell her
that you seem upset?
No, not necessary.
[sighs] Hey, uh...
did you get that action figure
you left at my house?
No, ma'am.
All my troops are present
and accounted for.
Got it.
Thanks, Rufus.
[door squeaks closed]
[exhales]
-[door closes]
-[phone chimes]
[clicks]
Nina, hi. It's Joe.
Listen, I just saw something.
[stammers] I can't explain it.
Hey, I, um...
Listen, I think I need to show it to you,
all right?
I'm gonna be home all night.
[ringback tone]
Oh, come on, come on.
Tyler.
I've been waiting for you.
Tyler!
Jesus, Kinsey,
just give it a rest for tonight.
Tyler! Look, [sighs] I know things
aren't great with us right now,
-but I really--
-You told me to be done with you,
so I'm done.
I actually feel good for once,
so please just stay out of my hair.
Those kids that drowned in the cave
were Dad's friends.
His best friends.
Lucas, Jeff, and Kim.
-They'd all just graduated.
-[suspenseful instrumentals]
Dad never told us.
Maybe that's why
he never wanted to come back here.
Even if it meant abandoning the keys.
[hushed, indistinct whispering]
You hear that?
Seriously? You want to do this right now?
It's coming from outside.
-[door opens]
-[heavy sigh] Shit.
[gate squeaks open]
It's in here.
[Tyler] Perfect. [sighs]
This is going to be a fun key.
[whispering continues]
You know, we can just ignore it.
Ignore the magic
that's literally calling out for us
to find it?
Ever heard of a siren song?
[whispering intensifies]
[Kinsey] It's in here.
[vase rattles]
[gate squeaks closed]
[item rattling in vase]
-Wait, you're not actually gonna--
-[shattering]
Unbelievable.
[whispering stops]
It looks like a starfish.
[Tyler sighs]
That's clearly a flower.
[dubious instrumentals]
I wonder where it goes.
Gee, maybe it's the, uh...
the glowing tree?
[Kinsey] We need to see what it does.
Actually, we don't.
-[sighs] I want you with me.
-[owl hoots]
These keys, they're our legacy.
And they're something
that connects us with Dad.
I think that means they're worth the risk.
And like you said,
the keys are weapons, too.
If we're somehow gonna have to fight
this Well Lady,
wouldn't it be smart for us to know
how they all work?
[key cranks]
[commotion and rumbling]
Kinsey?
Look.
[continued commotion]
[jars crinkle through pine straw]
[mellow instrumentals]
[jar twinkles]
-[whoos and laughing inside jar]
-[Kinsey] That's Dad flying.
They're memories.
Like in the candy boxes in my head,
but they're in paint jars.
Whose memories would be in paint jars?
[jar twinkles]
[Tyler] That's Dad and his friend Lucas.
[young Russell] Hey, Duncan,
what'd I say about snooping? Out, now.
[Kinsey] They're Duncan's memories.
[jar twinkles]
Okay, show me how it works.
All you have to do
is think about
what you want to look like.
-[neck opening crinkles]
-[key crunches]
[whoosh]
And that's what you chose.
Oh, my God, Tyler.
You have to see this.
There's a key
that can change the way you look.
-What is it?
-[breathes shakily]
-[grunting and groaning]
-[Lucas] No, Rendell! No!
-No!
-[whack]
It's kids from that photo that--
[crying out]
-The ones that drowned.
-[Kim] No, no, no!
What did you do?
Except obviously they didn't.
-[Kim cries]
-[young Duncan] Rendell?
Memories aren't perfect.
They're very subjective.
They're often distorted.
Does that...
does that look distorted to you?
[heavy breathing]
I can't believe this.
This isn't Dad.
He wouldn't even kill spiders
in the house!
He would never do something like this.
This is...
This is why
he didn't wanna come back here.
[dubious instrumentals fade to silence]
Joe?
Joe, it's Nina.
I got your message.
-[phone clicks]
-[keyboard clacking]
[ringback tone]
[phone rings]
Joe?
[suspenseful instrumentals]
[sharp crescendo]
Joe! Joe!
-Joe! [cries out and gasps]
-[plastic rustles]
-[gasping and groaning]
-[keyboard clacking]
[ringback tone]
[woman] Nine-one-one,
what's your emergency?
[gasps, stammers] My friend's dead.
He's not breathing.
There was a plastic bag over his head.
-[gasping]
-Where are you now?
I'm at his house: 4020 Lowell Drive.
-[pants]
-We have officers nearby.
-[heavy thud]
-[gasps]
[eerie instrumentals]
[shallow breathing]
[creaking]
[light crackling]
[suspenseful instrumentals]
[police sirens in the distance]
[sharp crescendo]
[instrumentals intensify,
then fade to silence]
[lively instrumentals]