[lively instrumentals]
[song intensifies, then fades to silence]
[burner ticks then ignites]
[serene instrumentals]
[chopping]
[pot rattles]
Ready with the celery?
Ready.
This was a great idea, Rufus.
I think Nina and the kids
are really gonna like it.
A good meal is important after a battle.
Right.
[upstairs commotion]
How much longer is he going to stay here?
[Ellie] Not much longer.
[Rufus] Not to break rank,
but you said that two weeks ago.
I need you to hang in there.
You remember the rule, right?
We can't let anyone know he's here.
[seagulls caw in distance]
[dubious instrumentals]
No breakfast?
We're making a soup
to take over to the Lockes.
Figured it was the least we could do.
Terrible what happened to them.
The kid that showed up,
it was the same kid
that murdered Rendell, right?
Talk about a dog with a bone.
Rufus, will you go down and see if we have
another can of tomatoes, please?
Where were you last night?
Did you somehow have a hand
in this, Lucas?
If anyone had a hand in what happened
at Key House...
it was you, Ellie.
-[Mr. Grady] You take care now, Kinsey.
-[Kinsey] Thanks, Mr. Grady.
[door closes]
Another casserole.
Is it weird that when you die...
almost die,
people bring you food?
[Kinsey] Totally.
I guess it's nice that people care.
Yeah. I'm sure they're all super stoked
that we lured a psychotic killer
into their nice little town.
Here, let me help.
[dishes clatter]
[Tyler sighs]
What are you thinking about?
I don't know.
How messed up this all is?
Dodge is the reason Dad's dead
and she got what she wanted.
She got the Head Key.
Sam said she's gonna use it
to try and open the black door.
Black door?
Yeah, it's in the sea caves.
My friends and I went down there
to film our movie.
I was checking the caves out
and found the door, way in the back.
I know you told me not to.
-[chair backs rattle]
-So, what's behind it?
I don't know.
-I didn't know how to open it.
-[inhales]
That's why Dodge wanted the Head Key.
Somebody has this information
in their brain.
Okay.
Who?
One of Dad's old friends?
I mean we know they used the keys
and they went down to the sea caves
at least once.
-I want to see it.
-I'm not sure
that's a good idea.
We lost track of time down there
and then the ocean came in.
We almost drowned.
Two fifteen is low tide.
[scoffs] You should've come with me
the first time.
Oh, my gosh! [laughs]
Look at all this stuff.
Yeah. Random people
have been dropping stuff off
-all morning.
-So nice that they care.
[faucet runs]
Mm! That is pretty good.
And you guys are cleaning!
Thanks so much, guys, for chipping in!
Why don't I go get started on the study?
[Nina exhales]
That was weird, right?
[vacuum hums loudly]
Mom?
[louder] Mom?
-[vacuum powers down]
-Sorry. [chuckles]
I thought I could save it,
but it's a goner.
[Nina sighs]
[Nina groans]
[Tyler] Here, I can help.
It's fine! It's done. See?
[Nina sighs]
Oh.
Oh, honey.
You being back in this room, it...
it must be...
[sharp inhale] Hey...
what you did to Sam...
you had to.
It was self defense.
You saved our whole family.
I don't want you to ever think
that you didn't do the right thing.
And if you want to talk
about anything that happened,
I'm here for you.
If you don't, that's okay, too.
Do you?
Mom? [stammers]
Want to talk about it?
Any of it?
I'm okay.
But no emotion is wrong here.
You should feel
however feels right to you, okay?
Okay?
Okay.
Good.
[Nina sighs]
[Nina] Oh.
I decided to move that old cabinet
in here.
Gives the room a whole different energy.
I might make some more changes
in here, too.
What the hell?
[tense instrumentals]
Come on.
What are you doing?
Looking for her stash.
-[rustling]
-She's clearly drinking again.
She's acting a little off.
We're all a little off right now.
It doesn't mean she's drinking.
Kinsey, you know the cycle.
First, she gets all happy,
carefree, then she'll get weird
and emotional for a while,
and after that, she'll just... shut down,
won't get out of her bed.
Don't tell me
you don't remember how this goes.
Of course I remember. I'm just saying--
-[door closes]
-Spearmint.
I smelled it on her breath.
She reeks of it.
-[drawer opens]
-[hushed] Shit.
Can't say I'm surprised.
Nothing that's been going on
makes any sense to her.
Is it our fault?
[drawer closes]
That we've been lying to her,
about the keys, about everything Sam said.
I dunno. I just... [sighs]
I just wanna find the booze
and throw it out.
[dramatic instrumentals]
What are you guys doing?
Nothing.
-Uh...
-We're just helping Mom.
Yeah, she, um...
she lost her phone, so...
What are we gonna do about Dodge?
She took all our keys.
You know what? Letting us handle it
right now is helpful.
Come on. Let's go downstairs.
I'll make you chocolate chip pancakes.
Hmm?
[doorbell rings]
[door opens]
[birds chirping]
-Detective.
-I hope I'm not intruding.
-Did you forget something?
-No.
I just wanted to check in on you.
Not in an official capacity,
just as a Matheson neighbor
seeing how you're holding up.
Hope that's okay.
Of course. Come on in.
Sure I can't get you some tea, Detective?
No, thank you.
And please call me Daniel.
[fire crackles]
How about something to eat?
You'd be helping me out.
Chances are if you name it,
-we've got too much of it.
-[chuckles]
Right.
The blessing and the curse
of living in a small town.
Everybody knows everything,
and most people
like to show their concern with food.
For sure.
You should see the collection.
Now, if Vincenzo shows up
with his lasagna--
I should call you?
You should consider that lasagna
the bright side
of an otherwise terrible situation.
[Nina slurps from mug]
You know, you could go anywhere.
Maybe getting out of town
would do you guys some good.
My brother-in-law Duncan offered us
his place up in Boston, but...
I think we're better off here.
Getting back to normal. [sighs heavily]
We're fine. [takes a breath]
[continued slurping]
[dramatic instrumentals]
[Daniel inhales slowly]
If you ever want to talk...
I know we don't know each other very well,
but sometimes that helps. I can be--
Thank you, Daniel.
Right.
Well, you've got my number
in case you need anything.
Either police-related or otherwise.
Take care, Nina.
[Nina takes a deep breath]
[retreating footsteps]
[door opens and closes]
-[somber instrumentals]
-[door squeaks shut]
[sighs]
[sniffles]
[liquid sloshes]
[pouring]
[eerie instrumentals]
-[gasps]
-[thudding]
[indistinct screaming]
-[sharp crescendo]
-[glass shattering]
-[gasps]
-[mug shatters]
[heavy breathing]
[somber instrumentals]
[cries softly]
[sniffles]
[door opens]
[shattered pieces clanking]
[exhales sharply]
[door squeaks open]
[pieces rattle]
[door squeaks shut]
[key clicks in lock]
-Are you okay?
-Oh, yeah,
I'm fine.
I'm just moving some things around
in here.
[dramatic instrumentals]
[faucet runs]
-[dish clanks]
-[phone buzzes and chimes]
[doorbell rings]
Why are you following me?
It's Jackie. She just texted.
Then why does she need to ring the bell?
-Hi.
-Hey, Kinsey.
-Did you guys carpool?
-[Gabe] No,
actually, we just, um...
We randomly got here
at the exact same time. [laughs]
-[curious instrumentals]
-And it gets weirder.
[birds chirping]
[bags rustle]
Dueling chowders.
Looks like you're not hurting
for comfort food.
No, this is... this is great.
Oh, my goodness!
[Nina chuckles]
The cavalry has arrived. [laughs]
Hi, I'm Nina.
I'm Jackie. It's so nice to meet you.
I just wish it was another time,
you know, different circumstances.
People come into our lives
exactly when they should.
[Nina inhales sharply]
Or so they say. [chuckles]
-Hi, I'm Gabe.
-[Nina] Hi, Gabe.
So...
do I have you two to blame for the fact
that I hardly ever see my kids?
-[Gabe laughs]
-Maybe?
[Nina cackles]
I'm joking!
I'm thrilled
that you guys are forming relationships.
-Mom!
-Oh, I'm not talking about romantic ones.
I mean, my God, I... [laughs]
I don't even pretend to know,
but friendships, friendships...
are the...
foundation that we stand on.
I really believe that.
I'll just say they're lucky
to have you guys.
Really! [laughs]
Especially given recent events.
Yeah, well, [laughs] we like hanging out
with them, too, so...
[doorbell rings]
Mm! Don't be strangers, okay?
This is as close as we'll get
to attending our own funerals.
[sighs]
[retreating footsteps]
Okay, let's go upstairs.
[chuckles] You wanna, um...
You wanna go somewhere and talk?
-[birds chirping]
-[door opens]
[Ellie] Hi, Nina.
Hi.
Rufus,
do you want to go and find Bode?
-I think he's upstairs in his room.
-Ten-four, ma'am.
[Ellie chuckles]
[Ellie laughs]
Thanks.
When I heard what happened to you guys,
I just felt sick.
Especially after Joe's memorial.
I am so sorry, Nina. I really am.
Don't be.
You were hurting
and I was interrogating you...
-I should've been more understanding.
-...and for what?
[stammers] I was just trying...
[sighs] I don't know.
Have you ever had that experience
in life, where...
[heartfelt instrumentals]
it just doesn't make any kind of sense
and...
you're so angry
about why things are the way they are?
[chuckles]
Yeah. I have.
You wanna come in?
-Yes.
-[laughs]
I want to apologize...
for bailing on the 5k and...
at that party...
I was a dick.
I shouldn't have left.
It really hurt me.
I'm so sorry.
I know.
Don't do it again.
Ellie?
[gasps] Kinsey. [sighs]
I'm so glad you guys are all okay.
Thanks.
Is everything okay with you?
-[tense instrumentals]
-Me?
Sure, why?
You haven't been approached
by anyone strange?
An unusual visitor?
Um--
Like say a very pretty girl
about yea high, dark hair?
[deep exhale] No.
Haven't seen anyone like that.
Okay. Good.
Okay.
[laughs] You have to take, like,
four casseroles with you.
[laughs] Do you have Vincenzo's lasagna?
Sadly, no.
-[kisses]
-I should get back up to Gabe.
[Bode] Mom! Mom!
[Nina] Aw...
Did you know
that Rufus has a P51 D Mustang?
-That's a car?
-An aircraft.
A model airplane.
Bode wants to come over
and work on it with me.
Yeah. If it's okay.
[Nina] Yeah, it sounds like fun.
Well, if that's okay with you, of course.
Might do him some good, you know,
to get out of the house for a bit.
Sure. Of course.
-Thanks, Mom.
-Have fun.
-Thanks, Ellie.
-[Ellie] Sure.
[Bode] Come on, Rufus! [mimics airplane]
Hey,
you got into Parsons, that's awesome.
Oh, yeah. [laughs] Thanks.
I wasn't snooping by the way.
That was just like sitting there.
It's fine.
Well, you don't seem very excited
about it. [chuckles]
Yeah, I dunno. I used to think I would be.
Should I be?
[scoffs] I'm not going to tell you
how to feel.
-That's very smart of you.
-Mm.
Although, if I was speaking selfishly,
I can't say that I'd be thrilled
at the idea of you being away
the whole summer.
No?
Well, I think you'd be the only one
who'd miss me. [chuckles]
What? That's not true.
-You're the only one who's here, Gabe.
-[laughs]
Okay, Doug and Zadie,
they wanted to be here, okay?
[stammering]
And I haven't talked to Scot yet,
but I'm sure--
They're all still mad at me.
I get that.
I deserve it.
No, but I think they're all just
a little freaked out. I mean...
It's kinda crazy
what happened to you and your family.
Yeah, no shit.
When I heard that guy came back...
[scoffs] who does that?
What did he want? Was he after revenge?
What does my family have
that no one else in the world does?
-Like 19 chimneys?
-[scoffs]
No.
Oh, you mean like magical keys?
Yeah.
But how did he...
I mean, [stammers] I thought
that hardly anyone knew about those.
That may be a story for another day.
Okay. Sure, yeah.
Yeah, no rush...
Your secret's safe with me.
I hope you know that.
I do.
-[doorbell rings]
-Thank you.
[Nina] Kinsey!
Someone's at the door for you!
I'll be right back, okay?
[blows breath]
Your mum let me in.
[Scot chuckles]
She's really quite friendly.
Kept calling me "Scot with one T."
-It was--
-I thought you were pissed at me.
[stammers] I've been... I was.
Look, I really was.
But, you know,
then what happened
happened and I just...
I mean, that kind of thing is...
it's bloody unbelievable, isn't it?
[chuckles]
So it kinda puts everything else
into perspective, and...
yeah, it just...
it seems kinda silly to be mad now.
I'm glad.
Listen, Scot, you should know that I'm--
That you're sorry?
Yeah, I know you're sorry.
Yeah, I am. I'm really sorry,
but also, you know--
Why don't we just
consider that box ticked, yeah?
I only get like 30 minutes on break
from work
and I already spent half of that time
getting my poxy car started
and driving over here, so...
if it's all right with you,
I would like to spend
what little time we have...
giving you this.
[chuckles]
Not rocky road?
[takes a breath] Yeah, I thought...
maybe just, like, a little bit too soon
even for me. [chuckles]
[approaching footsteps]
Hey, Scot.
Hey.
Gabe just came by to,
you know, see how I was.
Right. Yeah.
[clears throat] Yeah, yeah.
-Come in. Hang out with us.
-No, no, no. I shouldn't. I, uh...
[stammers] I'm due back in a few.
And my car's acting up.
And also I need a--
I need a good few minutes
to get the old apron on nicely.
So, uh, I'll just... [stammers]
I'll see you soon.
[heartfelt instrumentals]
I'm really glad you're okay.
Thanks... for the mint chip.
Right.
[door opens]
[door closes]
[Gabe clears throat]
I should probably head out, too.
Oh. Okay.
But I'm gonna give him, like,
a minute's head start if that's cool.
[seagulls cawing]
This is not easy.
Beats being home.
Is it hard to be there
after what happened?
It's not really that.
It's just...
Tyler and Kinsey have been
keeping secrets from me again.
And it's super frustrating.
How do you know
they're keeping secrets from you?
Wouldn't that be secret?
They think they're protecting me.
But they're wrong.
Just because they're older
doesn't mean they're right.
What's up?
If your direct commander
wanted you to keep...
sensitive intel on an enemy classified,
would you,
under any circumstances,
disobey that order?
Do you have an enemy, too?
Or are we talking about mine?
[approaching footsteps]
[Lucas] Rufus.
Who's your little friend?
[tense instrumentals]
This is Bode.
Bode, this is...
my cousin.
We're really busy right now.
I can see that.
So, I didn't know that Rufus had a cousin.
Where are you from?
Nowhere in particular.
Move around a lot.
I like living with Ellie, though.
Sorry to hear
about what happened at your house.
Thanks,
but like Rufus said,
we're sort of busy right now.
[Ellie] Hey, guys!
Brought you some fresh cookies...
You said you were going to be out
all afternoon.
-Well, I just got back.
-[Ellie takes a deep breath]
You guys want some ice cream
to go with these?
Yeah!
[tense instrumentals fade]
[birds trilling]
[items rattle]
[handle clanks]
-[door squeaks open]
-[sighs]
[lively instrumentals]
[Kinsey] Mom?
Mom?
What's wrong?
[Nina exhales]
[stammers] I...
I broke this earlier.
It was in pieces and I put those pieces
in this cabinet and I--
-I... [sighs]
-[door squeaks closed]
I locked them in there.
And then when I opened it just now,
my mug... [exhales]
[sharp inhale] it was just sitting there!
Fixed! Like new,
like magic or something! [catches breath]
But that's insane.
[Nina inhales sharply]
[mug taps desk]
[Nina exhales]
-[dramatic instrumentals]
-[Nina breathes shallowly]
[approaching footsteps]
[door rattles closed]
[door rattles open]
[Nina gasps, exhales] See?
-[trembles]
-Yeah, I do.
It's not just this. The--
This morning, [stammering]
I looked into the mirror
and I saw...
me, but it wasn't really.
It wasn't a reflection.
She wanted me to join her, to...
to step into the mirror...
Kinsey, I know how this is gonna sound,
[inhales] but I think I did
step into the mirror once.
[Nina catches breath]
I think I got lost in there.
I don't know how, but...
Does this have something to do with Sam?
With those things he was asking you about?
With... with...
[exhales] these keys?
You're looking at me like I'm crazy.
I don't think you're crazy, Mom.
This all seems pretty crazy to me.
I think I need to talk to Tyler.
Good. Yes.
Talk to your brother. [inhales sharply]
[Nina exhales]
["How It Feels" by Ages And Ages
plays through headphones]
♪ ...put your head on my chest ♪
-That old cabinet Bode thought was a dud,
-[phone beeps]
it's not.
It can put things back together.
Mom's the one who figured it out.
She showed me how it works.
She made it fix Sally
right in front of me.
-[stammers] She's seen magic before.
-Yeah.
But she's retaining it.
She's even remembering it from way back.
She told me she remembered
getting lost in the mirrors.
[curious instrumentals]
[pages tearing]
-[door creaks closed]
-[lock clicks]
[sniffles]
[whimsical effects]
-[lock clicks]
-[door creaks open]
[scoffs]
[pages fluttering]
Definitely not crazy. [scoffs]
-[heartfelt instrumentals]
-[Tyler] What's different? Why now?
[Kinsey] It doesn't make any sense.
She's drinking.
[Tyler] Maybe that's why she can
suddenly remember.
It has to be. Right?
It's the only thing that's changed.
[Kinsey, hushed]
What are we supposed to do?
If she keeps drinking,
she'll keep remembering
and finally be on the same page as us...
We'd be able to tell her the truth
about everything that's been going on.
Same team.
For real this time.
But you know we can't let her.
So we lose her either way.
This really sucks.
[alarm rings and buzzes]
It's almost low tide.
We should go.
-[jacket rustles]
-Dad's jacket...
Yeah. It's gonna be freezing down there.
What happened to yours?
Uh... [sighs] I left it at Javi's party.
[deep breath] All right.
Let's go.
[birds chirping]
Don't you look gorgeous today?
[indistinct chatter]
I almost didn't recognize you.
I'll just see myself
back to the visitors' area.
[clicks mouse] Actually,
Ms. Erin is with Gustave right now.
Who?
Don't take your eyes off the quarter,
my friends.
Remember when a quarter
used to actually buy you something?
-[carnival music plays]
-And who even uses coins anymore?
They just sit around in dishes
and in drawers.
Why not just make them... [blows air]
-[fabric whips]
-disappear?
-[crowd oohs]
-[applause]
[Gustave] Great. Thanks, Randolph.
How about a round of applause
-[chair scrapes]
-for Randolph.
Now, I want you to see
what I'm gonna do here, okay?
This is gonna happen quick.
I'm going to bend this spoon
using just my mind.
-Oh my. Look at that. [snaps finger]
-[crowd oohs]
Randolph...
-[applause]
-[hushed] Hey, Vossie.
I got you a little something.
Well,
technically, it's a gift for me,
but you get to provide the key component.
[Gustave continues indistinctly]
-[scoffs] I made a pun.
-[applause continues]
[key dings]
Here's hoping Rendell shared
all his secrets with you.
[dubious instrumentals]
Spare me the weird stuff though, okay?
Just show me where he hid my Omega Key.
[instrumentals intensify]
-[waves crashing]
-[seagulls cawing]
[tripod rattles]
What is that?
Lighting stand.
How much further?
Kinsey?
[waves rumble in distance]
I make terrible, reckless decisions.
I'm aware.
Can we keep going?
I almost got the Savinis killed here.
Because I was so obsessed
with following those stupid whispers.
I thought taking out my fear
would make me feel better.
It just made me act without thinking.
-[tripod clatters]
-Being fearless didn't even
make a difference when it counted.
What are you talking about?
With Sam.
I should've grabbed his gun in the woods
the second he dropped it.
But I didn't.
Just like back in Seattle,
I should've grabbed that fire poker.
You didn't grab the poker
because you were protecting Bode.
I saw it in your head.
And what happened
when Sam dropped the gun?
I ran.
Yeah. You ran.
With Bode.
You kept him safe both times.
-[scoffs]
-You'll make it right with your friends.
Come on.
[retreating footsteps]
[dubious instrumentals]
[low pulsating]
[indistinct whispering]
Whoa.
[whispering continues]
What do you think's behind it?
Do we really want to know?
Kins?
[low pulsating continues]
"The keepers of the keys."
What happened down here?
[Tyler] Jeff, Kim, Mark, Lucas, Dad.
They're all dead.
So now there's just two left.
And we know Ellie won't be any help.
I tried earlier.
What about Erin Voss?
She's in a psych ward.
[chuckles]
Seriously?
Mom wrote the name of the hospital down.
I saw it in her room.
Do you remember that story
Javi told us about a...
about a woman
who came to Key House
and then went insane?
Turned into a vegetable?
Thought he was just full of shit, but--
Maybe not.
[scoffs] For once.
[stammers] If that's...
If that's what happened to Erin,
do you think it would make sense for Dodge
to wanna use that key on her?
Erin was Dad's girlfriend,
so he might've told her
where the key to the black door is.
I think we should go see Erin.
Try to warn her.
You go.
I'll stay with Mom.
[wheelchair rattles]
[Dodge] Aw, look at you guys.
So happy.
-Too bad it couldn't last...
-[indistinct chatter]
Ready?
[tense instrumentals]
[neck opening crinkles]
-[key cranks in opening]
-[whoosh]
Huh.
Good old Matheson Academy.
Where's the other you?
Way to peak in high school.
[door creaks open]
[breaks whine]
[birds chirping]
[dramatic instrumentals]
[dubious instrumentals]
-[screen chimes open]
-To making the impossible possible.
To us, the keepers of the keys.
[glasses clink]
[cover slaps closed]
-[screen chimes open]
-[chatter on screen]
[screen chimes open and closed]
[screen chimes open]
[young Erin] Where do you want to hide it?
[young Erin] What are you doing here?
Hi, Erin.
So you're not brain dead.
You're stuck in here...
trapped in your own poor little mind.
Don't know how you managed that, but...
now I do know
where you hid the Omega Key.
[pen clicks]
-[scribbling]
-Oh. Ms. Erin's a popular one today.
-[indistinct chatter]
-She has a visitor?
[nurse] Mm-hmm.
A beautiful young woman. Like yourself.
[suspenseful instrumentals]
[door creaks open]
[young Erin bangs on door]
Let me out!
[rattles door] Let me out! Please!
-[key cranks in opening]
-[banging continues]
[key clinks and cranks in lock]
[seagulls cawing]
[dubious instrumentals]
[sharp inhale]
[toy cracks]
[Kinsey] Ms. Voss? Hi.
I'm Rendell's daughter, Kinsey.
Rendell.
I'm his daughter.
You guys were really close once.
That bracelet you're wearing
in the picture,
I have it now.
Ms. Voss...
we're worried that someone might try
to get inside your head.
[sighs] I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry I bothered you.
[strained] Dodge...
Dodge?
What, is she here?
[dramatic instrumentals]
The picture?
[Erin struggles to speak]
[Erin whimpers]
[strained] Dodge...
That's Lucas.
[stammers] Dodge.
Dad's best friend.
Dodge.
Are you saying he's Dodge?
[neck opening crinkles]
-[key cranks in opening]
-[whoosh]
[instrumentals intensify]
[opening crinkles]
[key dings]
[sentimental instrumentals]
-[door creaks closed]
-[Nina moans]
[lock clicks]
[Nina grunts and retches]
-[Nina coughs and exhales]
-[faucet runs]
[sighs]
-[faucet drips]
-[door opens and closes]
-[hopeful instrumentals]
-[exhales]
Rendell!
[instrumentals soften]
Mom?
-[somber instrumentals]
-It's me. I was...
I was just taking out the trash.
I thought... [gasps]
[trembles] The cabinet...
I thought maybe...
-[catches breath]
-It's okay.
[screams] No!
[Nina crying]
[urn shatters]
[heavy breathing]
Mom.
I'll take care of it.
-[Nina exhales sharply]
-[heartfelt instrumentals]
-Mom?
-[scoffs]
[Nina] I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
I know.
Mom, I know what you tried to do.
And I get why you did it.
I probably would've tried the same thing.
Why didn't it work?
You saw it before. It was...
it was like--
Magic.
Yeah.
It is magic.
We've tried to tell you before,
but you wouldn't remember.
Then tell me.
[sighs] I thought I could fix it.
Bring him back.
That I could fix us.
I should have protected you.
All of you. [sniffles]
[sighs] It's my fault Sam came after us.
[scoffs] I moved us here. [sniffles]
Mom, you are not to blame for Sam.
That I can promise you.
And you don't have to fix us.
Look, I know it's hard...
but you can't go back to drinking.
You just can't.
[owl hoots in distance]
We need you.
Okay?
[heartfelt instrumentals continue]
-[light clicks on]
-[ominous instrumentals]
I visited Erin today.
Took a stroll...
through that troubled head of hers.
I saw where Rendell hid the Omega Key.
He put it inside his own head.
They went in there together.
How sweet is that?
Ty. Erin pointed to a picture of Lucas.
-[hushed indistinct whispering]
-She called him Dodge.
Is that even possible?/
-Could they be the same person?
-[key dings]
[ominous instrumentals fade to silence]
[lively instrumentals]