[lively instrumentals]
[song intensifies, then fades to silence]
[Daniel] Here you go, two lattes.
It's perfect.
Thanks for suggesting this.
[folk music plays softly]
Six years of sobriety,
just... poof. [scoffs]
Slips happen.
They don't erase the progress
that you've made.
That day at our house
when you came by to check on us,
you knew, didn't you?
I suspected.
Everybody's recovery is different,
but what worked for me
was small steps.
It's all about tomorrow,
not the next year,
or the next five.
I just feel stuck in today.
[scoffs] Whatever step
that's supposed to be.
Matheson...
[taps table] was supposed to be
our fresh start.
I thought I'd feel closer to my husband,
connect some dots about his past,
[inhales] but it hasn't quite worked out
the way I hoped. [sighs]
Maybe living here...
is not healthy for me...
or my kids.
[Nina sighs]
-[owl hooting]
-Where's Ellie?
It's only been an hour.
[Bode] She should've been here by now
with the crown.
[Tyler] We just need to wait,
and stay ready.
What happens if Mom comes home?
This'll all be over by then.
[insects trilling]
Uh... Guys?
Look!
-[suspenseful instrumentals]
-[gravel crunching]
I hope you don't mind,
I invited some friends.
Shit.
[dramatic instrumentals]
[indistinct cracking]
Just... a scare tactic.
Shadows are just shadows.
[car rattles]
[car creaks upwards]
[crashes]
Get inside, now!
[all panting]
Help me barricade the door!
[desk scrapes on floor, thuds door]
-[instrumentals soften]
-[Kinsey] What do you see?
-There's nothing out there.
-[Bode sighs] I don't like this.
[Kinsey] Where did she go?
[Tyler] Did you lock the side door?
[ominous instrumentals]
[hushed indistinct whispering]
[whispering intensifies]
[Tyler] It's too quiet.
I'm gonna go check upstairs.
Not without me.
[Bode] Well, you just can't leave me here.
-[Kinsey] Tyler?
-[shoes squeak on floor]
[lid clanks]
-[Tyler] Stop!
-[shadow wails]
[Tyler gasps, thuds against wall]
[shadow screams]
Tyler!
[Dodge, gruff] Where is it?
-[shadow shrieks]
-[clicks light]
[Tyler chokes and gasps for air]
-[Tyler coughs]
-It's the lights.
That's what stops them!
-Okay, turn on all the lights.
-[Tyler breathes heavily]
-[light dings]
-[rattling breath]
-[shadow shrieks]
-[Tyler gasps, pants]
-[crashing]
-[Tyler] The kitchen.
[crashing continues]
[shattering]
[continued crashing]
[rattling, then silence]
[Kinsey exhales sharply]
[all breathing heavily]
-They're looking for the Omega Key.
-[Bode sighs]
-It's safe, they can't get to it.
-[crickets chirping]
[pants] Keep the lights on.
As long as they're on,
they can't touch us.
-[toy sword thumps]
-[Tyler exhales sharply]
-[zipping]
-[Kinsey] What are you doing?
[Bode] Making a weapon
with the Matchstick Key.
[panting] Come and get me,
Shadow Monsters!
[whooshing]
[suspenseful instrumentals intensify]
[light clanks off]
[indistinct whispering]
Uh-oh.
-Fuse box.
-It's in the basement.
I'll go turn the lights back on,
you guys distract Dodge.
[toy sword whooshes]
[continued whispering]
[Dodge, gruff] Give me the key.
[yelling] Get back!
There are more flashlights upstairs,
come on!
[suspenseful instrumentals intensify]
[shoes squeaking on floor]
[whispering intensifies]
[Kinsey thuds down stairs]
[sharp crescendo]
-[flashlight clatters]
-[Kinsey grunts]
[heavy breathing]
Flashlights have to be in here somewhere.
Where are they?
[Kinsey breathes heavily]
-[sharp crescendo]
-[Kinsey screams]
[pants]
-[whack]
-[Kinsey screams]
[dragging]
[Kinsey screams hysterically]
-[instrumentals intensify]
-[match flicks]
[shadow shrieks]
[shadow growls]
[indistinct whispering]
[Kinsey gasps]
[instrumentals soften]
[Dodge, gruff] Where is the key?
[yelling] You're not gonna hurt us
anymore!
[shadow screams]
[continued screaming]
[indistinct groaning]
[shadow crackling, struggling]
Holy shit.
[panel squeaks open]
[pants]
[switches flicking]
[electrical whirring]
Where did she go?
[Kinsey] Guys?
Come see this!
[dubious instrumentals]
[heavy breathing]
Did I kill her?
[Kinsey sighs]
[Bode] After I stabbed her,
her shadow melted downstairs.
She's still breathing.
[Tyler] Whatever you did,
she's out cold.
[stammers] Where's the crown?
[Tyler] I don't know,
but first things first,
is the Omega Key still safe?
[door creaks open]
Affirmative.
[both sigh in relief]
-What do we do with her now?
-[Kinsey] We can't kill her.
Why not?
She's the reason why Dad is gone.
I mean, we literally can't kill her.
Ellie said Echoes can't be killed
by normal means.
Maybe we can put her back
in the well house.
We'll need the Echo Key for that,
but Ellie has it.
What if we send her back
where she came from?
What are you talking about?
The Black Door!
We use the Omega Key
to open the Black Door and send her back.
The last time that door was opened,
Dad's friend got possessed by a demon
and he had to bludgeon him to death.
What happens if she wakes up?
If you have any better ideas,
I'm all ears.
[sighs]
[Bode] Wait,
so we're going to the sea caves?
No, you're not,
we are.
You're staying here.
Fine, but I'm gonna go check on Rufus.
He and Ellie were supposed to come back
with the crown.
If Ellie's in trouble, he could be too.
That's not a good idea.
Well, I can't just stay here!
Rufus is my friend,
and I don't care what you guys say,
[retracts sword]
I'm going.
Just don't do anything stupid.
-You either.
-[Tyler sighs]
[Tyler] If we're gonna carry her
all the way down to those caves,
we're gonna need some help.
[knocking at door]
Demon Disposal Service, you rang?
-Thanks for coming.
-[Gabe] No problem.
-[crickets chirping]
-We brought back up too.
[sighs heavily] Scot told us
you needed help.
Yeah, and the FOMO was real.
Wow, Eden, I... I did not expect this.
Well, I was feeling a little bit generous
after my brush with death.
Plus, I don't know who this bitch is,
but she's not about to let
some rando demons run through my town.
Well put.
Yeah, we would've called
the rest of the Savinis,
but you know, they still have
a little bit of "Cave PTSD," so...
-[Scot laughs]
-It's okay, this is awesome.
[long exhale] And I'm sorry
I freaked out earlier.
I... Mostly I'm just sorry
that you didn't think
you could tell me
about all this stuff sooner.
Yeah, I didn't... I didn't think
that was gonna go over so well.
-[heartfelt instrumentals]
-I get that,
but I'm not scared.
Then you're way ahead of me.
-[chuckles]
-And I'm not going anywhere.
[Scot clears throat]
Sorry, sorry. It was--
It was nice, like a really sweet moment,
but I just feel like
we have a demon to be dealing with, and...
You know, uh, so where is she?
He-- It-- [stammers]
I don't know what the pronoun is,
demon non-binary. What are we doing?
[dramatic instrumentals]
Not exactly what I picture
when I think of "formidable demon."
[Scot] Really? Pretty much
exactly what I was expecting.
Oh, come on. Where are the fangs?
Where are the horns?
-Where are the--
-No, no, this is all--
This is all meant to lull you
into a false sense of security.
You know, the perfect bone structure
and the impeccable style--
Guys, can we focus?
Where'd you put the flashlights?
I'll get them.
[camera shutters]
What?
Do not post that.
Fine.
[cover rustles]
-[insects trilling]
-[owl hooting]
[Scot stammers] I guess it makes sense
really, doesn't it?
Demons have to be disposed of properly,
so throwing them behind a big demon door
just seems logical, doesn't it? [laughs]
You know, that being said, I don't know,
I feel like this is a little bit doomed,
you know?
I'm not saying like it is doomed,
but I definitely feel like
we're walking towards the Gates of Mordor.
[Eden] Can I ask a question?
Besides, Scot, can you stop talking?
[Gabe] Yes, go, Eden.
[Eden] So what happens if she wakes up?
Like do we have a plan for that?
-[sighing]
-[Tyler] I brought a knife.
[Eden] Oh, you're gonna have a knife-fight
with the demon?
[Kinsey] You can't kill her with a knife.
[Tyler] Might at least give us
a head start.
Okay, any more questions?
Yeah, can we just get this over with?
[waves crashing]
[dubious instrumentals]
[Kinsey sighs] How's the tide situation?
It's just past full-low.
We're okay if we go now.
Are we?
Look, no one has to go down.
No, we're going.
I mean, at least I am.
Me too.
Yeah, of course.
Not one to resist some good,
old-fashioned peer pressure, am I?
I'm in.
-[swelling instrumentals]
-[bike chain rattling]
[Bode yelling] Rufus?
Ellie?
Rufus?
Rufus! Rufus!
Rufus,
wake up!
Help!
[waves crashing]
[dubious instrumentals]
Here we go again.
Watch your head.
[Scot] It's worse than last time.
-[grunting]
-How did you guys find this place?
[Kinsey] We were gonna shoot the movie
in here.
[laughs] Yeah, no, I would've quit
if I hadn't already quit.
[Gabe] Go ahead. I got it.
[groaning and sighing]
[Jackie] Okay.
-[Tyler grunts]
-Well, that was fun.
[hushed indistinct whispering]
[Kinsey sighs]
[low droning]
You're hearing that, right?
You mean the really scary
rumbling sound?
[feet shuffling]
[heavy breathing]
[grunting and groaning]
[Scot] What do you suppose
is on the other side of this?
Nothing good.
Yup. Well, unless you're a demon.
Let's just do this and get out of here.
I don't think we should.
[Tyler] It was your idea!
Does this feel right to you?
If you got any better ideas, I'm all ears.
Best-available idea doesn't make something
a good idea.
Uh, okay, I hate to break up
a good old sibling squabble,
but I am very worried about these tides
and I do have some experience
to back that up.
Shit. Yeah, we should hurry.
That is not what you said before.
Yeah, it took a lot longer
to get down here than I thought.
[rustling]
[Jackie] Is she waking up?
Oh, no. No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
[Dodge moans softly]
Hey, guys, we gotta do this now.
Are you sure?
We can't take it back.
Kinsey, we're here.
We can end this...
-[low droning]
-for Dad.
-[suspenseful instrumentals]
-All right.
Okay...
Kinsey will unlock the door,
the rest of you, stay on it.
If something happens, just close it.
I'll carry Dodge to the edge
and throw her through.
And if anything exits that door
when we open it?
Wait, hold on. Anything like what?
Ellie said they were like glowing bullets.
Just don't let them hit you, okay?
[all murmur]
[hushed indistinct whispering]
[key scrapes and clicks in lock]
[lock thuds and cranks]
[door rattles and releases]
[heavy sighs]
[door creaks open]
[loud rumbling]
That's...
What is that?
[Gabe] Yeah.
-[whirring]
-[Kinsey] Look out!
[light beam whizzes past]
[both grunting]
-[Gabe] There's another one.
-[whizzing]
What are you doing?
[Tyler grunts]
[Dodge] No!
No! No!
[Dodge gasping] Tyler, don't!
[screaming] No!
[dramatic instrumentals]
No!
[yelling] Close the door!
[door creaks]
[light beams whizzing]
[whizzing and popping]
-[all grunting]
-[door slams]
[lock clicks]
[heavy breathing]
[Scot exhales sharply]
[all sighing]
[Scot chuckles]
[owl hoots in the distance]
[door knob rattles]
[doors rattle open]
Okay, I hope
we never have to do that again.
I don't think that's actually an option.
Is it weird that I kinda had fun?
No weirder than what we just saw.
Tyler, Kinsey, you guys were awesome.
We all did it, everybody.
Do you guys want some food
or something before you leave?
I mean,
it's the least we can do to thank you.
I've always got an appetite.
[Jackie] Yeah, I'm down!
-Kins?
-[retreating footsteps]
You got a minute?
[heartfelt instrumentals]
Uh... [chuckles]
I know this probably isn't necessarily
the best time to do this, but, uh...
I've been thinking a lot about...
your notion
that Gabe and I both date you... [laughs]
and...
I've just gotta say that that's...
that's not gonna work for me.
So, if you're undecided, then... [scoffs]
then that is your decision.
I understand.
Right.
Great. So, I mean, we can be friends.
You know, great friends, I hope.
Right? Tried and true,
bonded by demons
and magic and all sorts. [laughs]
Yeah?
I hope so too.
[chuckling] Okay, so my mom
-is gonna live until she's 109.
-[giggling]
She has more energy than I had
when I was 20.
-Ooh.
-She comes up here to visit me sometimes,
but mostly because she wants
to clean my house.
[laughing] No, and you let her?
-Yes! Try and stop her!
-[laughs heartily]
I may be a cop,
but I am not saying no to Mom.
-[phone buzzing]
-Oh, uh...
[Nina clears throat]
Matuku.
Yeah.
[indistinct chatter]
Okay, on my way.
Police business.
Afraid so.
I, uh... I gotta go.
Of course. [chuckles]
[both laugh]
I really enjoyed this.
Yeah, me too.
[Nina laughs]
[dishes clatter]
[clicks tongue]
[folk music plays softly]
[indistinct police radio chatter]
[indistinct chatter]
Hey.
Your friend's okay.
They're gonna take him to the hospital
so he can get checked out.
You can go see him now, if you want.
Thanks.
[continued chatter]
-Bode.
-Are you okay?
-[distant police sirens]
-[sighs] I usually feel a lot better.
Well, what happened?
Where's your mom?
[stammers] I don't know.
Lucas used one of the keys
to turn himself into a lady,
with long, black hair.
That's Dodge.
Here.
Take this.
[dramatic instrumentals]
Rufus, you okay there?
Affirmative.
Sorry, kid, we gotta go now.
Goodbye, Bode.
Bye, Rufus.
[engine rumbles]
[engine revs]
[ambulance siren wails]
Where's Dodge?
[Tyler] She's gone, for good.
So you threw her through the door?
-In the cave?
-[Tyler] Yeah.
Are you sure it was Dodge?
Why would you ask that?
I went to Rufus' house, right?
Right.
When I got there, Rufus was knocked out.
So I called 911 and the police came,
and his mom was missing.
And then when he woke up,
he told me
-that Lucas did it.
-[Tyler] Wait, what?
Where's Ellie?
Nobody knows.
And since Lucas is Dodge,
I just wanted to make sure
you guys got rid of her.
Trust me.
She's gone.
We both saw her get swallowed up
in whatever was on the other side.
[Tyler sighs]
[Kinsey] Okay?
-[kisses]
-Okay? [pats legs]
We're safe now.
Okay. [sighs]
-[serene instrumentals]
-[birds chirping]
[dishes clinking]
-[sizzling]
-[spatula clatters in pan]
[rattling on stove]
[Duncan] Hey, late risers!
-Uncle Dunc!
-[Duncan] Hey...
What, you guys have a raucous night
or something last night?
-[sighs] Or something.
-[Nina] Get it while it's hot!
Look at this spread! Did you make this?
[Duncan] No, no, this was all your mom!
[muffled] Delicioso!
Does anyone know what happened
to Dad's car?
I was driving it to the store this morning
and something's wrong with the steering.
It was shaking and wobbling...
[laughs] I felt like
I was riding in a blender!
I guess I'll have to, uh,
-take it to the shop.
-[utensils clinking]
When I was at the store,
I saw Bernadette from school.
Nobody's heard a word about Ellie.
Nothing?
[Nina] No, so weird. What about Rufus?
He slept with some neighbors last night,
and his aunt and uncle are flying in
from Nebraska this morning.
[Nina sighs]
Anyway...
before everyone runs off,
we need to have a little family meeting.
It's important.
And you're gonna need to hear this too.
Okay...
What about?
[Duncan] Yeah.
I made a mistake
moving us here.
I thought it was a good idea at the time.
I wanted to learn more
about your Dad's past,
and I thought the change would do us good.
[heartfelt instrumentals]
I dragged all of you out here
against your wishes, and now,
we get to go back home.
[voice shaking]
This house is in good enough shape
for us to sell, and...
we can use that money
to buy a great new house in Seattle.
And that will be our house!
We'll just consider this
a necessary little side-trip...
At least, for me.
But now,
we get to go back to our normal lives.
[stammers] Okay.
Don't everybody jump for joy
all at once. [chuckles]
We actually like it here.
[Tyler] Yeah. I mean, it did seem
like a shitty idea at the time.
Now, we love it here!
I wouldn't say love it,
but I don't... I don't wanna move again.
Me either.
Seriously?
[stammers] You guys want to stay?
Yeah, definitely.
-I thought you guys hated this place.
-[Tyler] We did,
until... until we didn't.
Because we finally got good WiFi.
[all laughing]
And maybe Dad didn't always love it here,
but this place is still part of who he is.
We like being here....
where he lived.
[Duncan] I'm not sure that I get a vote,
but, um...
you're the best thing
to ever happen to this place...
-since at least the 1890s.
-[Nina chuckles] Okay.
Well, I'm just processing all of this.
[sniffles] I really felt
like I made a horrible mistake.
You didn't.
Okay?
[Bode] Uh... Hey, what about me?
[Nina laughs] Come on!
It's not a group hug without me!
[Nina and Duncan chuckle]
-[seagulls cawing]
-[water lapping]
[Bode] Dear Rufus,
I hope you're getting settled
at your uncle's house.
-[scribbling]
-We drove through Nebraska
on our way to Matheson.
Kool-Aid was invented there,
so it must be a pretty great place.
My mom has been helping
the police detective look for your mom.
[engine idles]
I know something weird happened
that night...
[Nina sighs heavily]
...and I promise you,
I'm going to figure it out.
At first, these keys were fun,
but now we know
that they're more than that.
They're important.
They're part of our family...
[heartfelt instrumentals continue]
and we need to protect them.
-[lid claps shut]
-We're the new Keepers of the Keys.
One more thing,
mail me a picture of the front door
of your uncle's house,
because if I do get back
that Anywhere Key,
I'm coming straight to Nebraska!
Your fellow soldier, Bode.
[birds chirping]
[waves crashing]
[lid clinks]
[ashes hiss into wind]
[lid clatters]
You're home now, Rendell.
We're home.
[heartfelt instrumentals fade]
So I guess you're stuck with me
all summer now.
You say that like it's a bad thing.
Hold on one sec.
Where are you headed?
Going fishing with Jackie.
Her parents have this,
like, ridiculous boat.
Wanna come?
I'm going to grab a bite at Phil's
with Gabe.
Phil's is trash!
Yeah, yeah!
-[opens door] Have fun!
-Yeah, you too!
[door closes]
So, I'll see you at six?
Yeah, perfect.
[mellow instrumentals]
[gears clicking]
[rushing effect]
[curtains rattle]
What's up? I'm Gabe.
Craft service?
[bike chain rattling]
[rushing effect]
I mean, that door was...
what the hell was that thing?
I don't know.
I think it has something to do
with the magic.
You think you have a key
that might open it, or...
[Kinsey] I should never have made you guys
go down there.
[Gabe] You didn't make us do anything.
I mean, I'm excited to be alive right now!
You just...
you have that effect on people.
You have this energy that I think
we'd all follow, anywhere.
You're a badass.
[Gabe] I like this Kinsey.
[kisses]
I should go.
I'll call you tomorrow?
[sighs] Sure.
Okay.
[dubious instrumentals]
[key clicks in opening]
[instrumentals intensify]
[key scrapes outward]
[indistinct chatter]
-["Devil" by Vive La Void playing]
-So...
where can a girl get a drink around here?
♪ I saw the devil
In a violent dream ♪
[women continues singing indistinctly]
[key clicks in opening]
[gasps]
What are you doing?
[key clicks in opening]
[click]
[gasping]
No.
-[whack]
-[thud]
[yelling] You're not gonna hurt us
anymore! [screams]
[woman continues singing indistinctly]
Guys?
Come see this!
[Kinsey breathes heavily]
[light beams whizzing]
[wound sizzles]
So, how are you feeling?
[sighs heavily] So hungry.
[thundering]
[thunder roars]