[whimsical instrumentals]
[drums pencil on paper]
[Nina] Want some syrup?
[Bode sighs]
Yes, please.
Duncan's on his way down from Boston.
So great to have him here
to help us get settled.
Why is everyone so quiet today?
We're not quiet.
Okay.
You don't remember seeing anything...
unusual last night?
You mean the mirror?
The one in Bode's room?
Yeah.
We'll get around to polishing it,
but... [sighs] it's way down on my list.
[doorbell rings]
[Nina sighs]
That's the hardware store delivery.
Okay. I've been thinking,
and maybe what happened last night
didn't happen
like we think it happened.
Mold.
This house is full of mold
and some mold makes people sick, Bode.
It makes them hallucinate.
It could explain
why Mom doesn't remember anything.
[Bode sighs]
The reason why she doesn't remember
is because she's a grown up.
That's how this stuff always works.
Only kids can get into Narnia.
[scoffs] This isn't The Lion, The Witch
and The "whatever," Bode.
This is the real world,
where everything makes sense except you.
Come here.
[commotion]
[Bode sighs]
[key clinks]
[faint echoing boom]
[faint whimsical instrumentals]
[Bode] Hey, Evil Kinsey reflection!
Are you just a mold hallucination?
Holy shit.
[Bode] You were saying?
[descending footsteps]
What the hell are you doing?
-[key rattles]
-[Tyler breathes heavily]
Bode?
Is this the only key you found?
-[Tyler softly pants]
-Yes.
Wait! What about the one
you took out of my bracelet?
The one you said could take you
anywhere in the world?
[stammers] I lost it.
[scoffs] You just lost a key
that could take you anywhere?
You were so excited about it.
-I don't get how you just lost it.
-[honking]
Even more reason
not to trust him with this one.
[Tyler] That's Javi.
If you want a ride, we got to go.
-Please, please just be normal today.
-[birds chirping]
You find any keys, don't touch them.
[door creaks shut]
[Kinsey] What was it like in there?
-I don't know. It was...
-[crow caws]
-like some kind of fun house from Hell.
-[snow crunching under steps]
[Kinsey] I can't believe
we're just going to school
like nothing insane is going on.
Some of the girls back in Seattle
used to take mental health days off
from school.
[sighs] How about a day
for processing the fact
that we live in a frickin' magical house?
-Do you think Dad knew about the keys?
-Please,
just shut up about it.
People think we're weird enough already.
Don't make it worse.
Hey, man.
This is my sister, Kinsey.
-[Javi] What up?
-Hey.
This house is crazy.
I've been hearing stories about it
since I was a kid.
-[Javi chuckles]
-Like what?
Okay.
So there's this one where this lady
just wandered in and she went nuts.
All right, she's like a vegetable now.
Lives in an insane asylum.
Sounds like total bullshit.
-Could be.
-[car door opens]
Who knows?
-[car door closes]
-[engine turns over]
[toy sword whooshes]
-[sword light clicks on]
-[curious instrumentals]
[floorboards creak]
[sword rattles mechanically]
[breathes heavily, gasps]
I am seeing multiple points of entry,
Captain.
[gruff imitation] Copy.
Let's stay on high alert.
[heavy breathing]
[sighs]
[door creaks open]
[loud bang]
[loud commotion]
-[toilet flushing]
-Hey.
[Bode sighs in relief]
[Duncan] Hot tip?
That's the best toilet in the house.
[hushed] Uncloggable!
-[patting]
-Yeah, good to know.
-[curious instrumentals continue]
-[Bode sighs]
Permission to speak freely, sir?
[gruff imitation] Go ahead.
I'm starting to think...
we may need some more powerful weapons.
[thudding]
[swords ting]
[faint indistinct whispering]
[Bode exhales in excitement]
[faint indistinct whispering continues]
[door handle rattles]
[door creaks open]
[curious instrumentals intensify]
[vacuum wheels rattle]
[whispering continues]
[whispering intensifies]
[suspenseful crescendo]
[bag thuds]
["Exits" by Foals plays]
♪ Now the sea eats the sky,
But they say it's a lie ♪
-♪ There's no birds left to fly ♪
-[car breaks whine]
-♪ We'll hide out ♪
-[gearshift cranks]
-[unlatches seat belt]
-Dude, this is a...
Yeah, I know. Pulled a hamstring
last week during practice.
Doctor says I shouldn't push myself.
What is her problem?
She just came out that way.
Here I am, being so chill
not asking you about last night.
-Last night?
-How's your ankle, man?
Oh, like you don't remember.
Hey, Brinker, what's up?
Come on, you and Eden.
What, this guy's been here like a day
and he's already tapping
Matheson's finest.
Yeah, I swear this was all me.
For real,
I was like your ass guru, essentially.
So. How was it?
[indistinct chatter]
[Tyler] Uh... [sighs]
It was...
[stammering] Yeah, it was cool.
It was good.
-[Brinker] Oh, yeah! Eden!
-[Javi laughs]
[Brinker laughs] Wow.
Locke, stock and two smokin' titties!
-You always take it too far, dude.
-[Brinker] Uh...
What?
[exhales heavily]
[door opens]
[door squeaks closed]
[knocking]
[woman] Hi.
Nina?
I'm Ellie Whedon.
My son Rufus has been taking care
of the grounds here.
Yes. Hi.
So nice to meet you. [laughs]
I brought you a little housewarming gift.
It's artisanal gin.
It's made right here in Matheson
by the Wheeler sisters.
They get a lot of tourists
at their distillery in the summer.
Oh, uh-- Thank you.
So, I hear your kids are going
to the academy.
I teach there, Phys Ed.
Part time so I can hang out with Rufus.
Oh, that's great.
Are you from here?
I am.
In fact, I went to the academy
with your husband.
You know, I think
I found a photo of you yesterday.
[Ellie] Wow. [chuckles]
He's cute.
Lucas was my boyfriend.
Also Rendell's best friend.
Rendell never mentioned him.
[phone chimes and buzzes]
[sighs] Sorry.
[phone dings]
Hello?
-[woman] Is this Mrs. Locke?
-Yes.
Hi, this is Bernadette
at the academy calling.
We still haven't received
your tuition payment plan.
Okay, um... I'm sorry.
Um...
The form must have gotten lost
in the shuffle.
-[dramatic instrumentals]
-[Nina continues in the background]
I should get going anyway. [sighs]
I'm really glad you're here, Nina.
Thanks. It was really nice to meet you.
-[curious instrumentals]
-[key rattles in lock]
[cabinet thudding]
[door handle rattles]
[birds cawing chirping]
[crow trilling]
[snow crunches under steps]
-[indistinct cawing]
-[lock rattles]
[exhales]
[sighs]
I think I scared you.
I didn't mean to scare you.
[stammers] That's okay.
I saw you at the ice cream store
the other day.
My name's Rufus.
I'm adopted.
I work here.
I'm an excellent employee.
Hi. I'm Bode. I live here.
We've got the same GI Joes.
[laughs] Except yours has an M16.
Mine's got an M60 machine gun.
Wow. [chuckles]
You sound like you're a weapons expert.
I've never actually handled a gun.
My mother says
[stammering] I'm an agent of peace,
but I do know all about weapons.
So...
what do you think is the best weapon
to use against an enemy
who you're not even exactly sure
what it is?
[Rufus exhales]
[keys jingle]
Come in here.
-[chains clank]
-[Rufus] This should do it.
If you need more traps,
I always leave the key ring
in the top drawer by the stove,
but you need to take care,
or you could end up losing a hand,
or at least a few fingers.
[rattling]
I could help if you want.
No. I have to handle this myself
I'm the reason she's out there.
You'll probably want
to camouflage it, too.
Unless your enemy's dumb.
Yeah, she's not dumb.
But the most important thing is bait.
You got to ask yourself,
what does my enemy most want?
What does she want?
["Leaving After Midnight"
by Hummingbird Hotel plays]
♪ You've been all alone ♪
-♪ I've been gone on this road so long ♪
-[dishes clink]
[waitress] Okay.
♪ The same old silver moon ♪
♪ Now I see what I got to do ♪
Wish I had your metabolism.
♪ Gone before the morning light ♪
♪ To kiss your lips
When you open up your eyes ♪
[ramekin clinks]
[radio plays faintly in the background]
[finger sizzles]
[birds cawing]
Could you tell me where the restroom is?
Sure. It's right through there.
Great.
[patrons laugh]
[register dings]
[indistinct chatter]
[dishes clatter]
[key rattles, then clicks in lock]
-[upbeat lounge music plays]
-[woman sings in foreign language]
[hangers clink]
[indistinct chatter]
[zipping]
[woman continues singing
in foreign language]
[key clicks and cranks]
["Alors On Danse" by Stromae plays]
-[singing in French]
-[glass shatters]
-[necklace jingles]
-[alarm sounds]
-[doors open]
-Alarm!
Alarm!
[continued singing in French]
[indistinct chatter]
[heavy breathing]
[whispers] I want you to choke me.
My turn.
[man exhales]
Too much.
Hey.
[man struggles]
Stop.
[in French] Let me go.
[man gasps]
[continued singing in French]
[song fades]
[indistinct chatter]
[exhales steadily]
[continued chatter]
[Scot] Kinsey, hey.
Hey, how's it going? I, um...
Listen, I wanted to offer my apologies
for yesterday.
I'm-- I'm terribly sorry.
Okay, um...
Look, I know that didn't sound genuine
and it's probably 'cause I'm English
and so I have the emotional range
of a scone. [laughs]
A what?
A scone. You know, the dry biscuity thing
that no one's ever very excited about?
Oh. A scone.
Right. See, even my pronunciation
feels repressed. [chuckles]
But you know, with that being said,
I really am sorry, Kinsey,
and I hope that you can forgive me.
I think you're a little too hard
on scones.
-[Scot laughs]
-[girl] Hey,
I am going to be a little bit late.
I'm going to get my hair blown out.
It's just how I see Amanda.
-Okay, but--
-[Eden] Hey,
you can reimburse me.
I'll see you later.
Who's Amanda?
[scoffs] She's my heroine.
All the Savinis now,
we're making a cinematic tour de fear.
It's a short film
we're calling The Splattering.
Wow.
Which I maintain should be called
The Spattering
because it is in fact blood spatter,
and not blood splatter,
but the Savinis maintain
that no one actually cares, so...
splattering.
Anyway, Eden's playing the lead.
-Eden?
-Yeah, she's actually pretty talented
when she's not draining the life force
out of me.
[chuckles]
Hey, if, I mean, if you want,
you could join us on set
and maybe I could apologize properly?
I'm making smoothies, so...
And I promise
there won't be anything
actually scary there, [laughs]
besides Eden's monstrous ego,
of course. [laughs]
Thank you.
Excuse me.
-Are you Mrs. Locke?
-Yes.
I'm Joe-- Do you mind?
Hi.
I'm Joe Ridgeway. Dean of 11th grade.
Your son Tyler is in my English class.
Oh, wow.
How's he doing?
Well, it's only been two days,
and I usually wait
until at least day three
before I make any big judgments
about my students' character.
-I see. [laughs]
-[chuckles]
I can already tell that he's a bright kid.
He's just quiet, that's all.
Right.
-Well, you know, we've had quite a--
-I do know.
And I'm going to look out for him.
You have my word.
-Thank you.
-You know, it's uncanny,
the way he reminds me of his father.
-You know Rendell?
-Oh, very well.
I was his teacher, too.
Really?
So you taught Ellie
[stammers] and Lucas
and all those other kids?
That I did. Wow. Such a tight knit crew.
Rendell always said
that he was a loner as a kid.
Hmm. Yeah, well... [inhales]
maybe he was when he was younger,
but after a certain point,
he and those friends of his
were always together,
cooking things up,
but they were all good kids.
Such a tragedy what happened to them.
Oh, [stammers] he never talked about them?
Huh.
-[eerie instrumentals]
-Not at all?
[receptionist] Mrs. Locke,
I just need one more signature from you.
Oh, and I better be going.
I got a class in a few minutes.
Listen, it was wonderful to meet you.
-You, too.
-All right.
-I'll see you soon.
-Yes, I hope so.
[indistinct chatter]
-Hey.
-Hi.
Are you here to sign up?
Uh...
No, I'm not.
I'm not really a big activities guy.
So, then why are you here?
I wanted to let you know that nothing...
happened between me and Eden.
You think I don't already know that?
Eden's my friend.
She told me everything.
I actually thought you were a decent guy
until this morning.
So, you don't need
to set the record straight with me...
but maybe instead you can go tell Javi
and Brinker what really happened.
No?
Not interested?
You know,
you can either be an asshole
or a good guy, Tyler.
You can't be both.
Hey, you here to sign up?
-Yup.
-Cool.
I just need your name
and your homeroom. There.
[ominous instrumentals]
Come sit down with me for a second.
Can you make it quick?
I've got hockey practice.
[Tyler sighs]
Tell me what you know about Sam Lesser.
I don't know. He's pretty weird, I guess.
Doesn't...
seem to have a lot of friends?
No, I guess not.
Why?
I was hoping that maybe
you could reach out to him.
He could really use the extra support.
-Is there a problem?
-Yeah.
Dad, my friends already give me
enough shit as it is.
They call me the guidance counselor.
[scoffs] Ouch.
[stammers] I'm just saying,
if I start dragging Sam around
like here's my freaky little pet,
they are gonna--
What? The world is gonna end?
Come on, give me a break.
You've got a lot of social power.
I've seen it,
and now I'm just asking you to use it.
-Dad, please.
-Actually...
I'm not asking.
-[indistinct chatter]
-[Nina] Tyler!
[sighs]
[birds chirping]
-I didn't mean to spy on you.
-[door closes]
I just-- I think it's great
that you're signing up for more stuff.
Maybe you can work on the newspaper,
the debate team or something--
Just give me a break, all right?
It's been two days.
I barely know my way to class.
I know, I'm sorry. I just...
I just want you guys to find
some happiness here.
I know.
Keep an eye out for Kinsey, okay?
She doesn't make friends as easily as you.
See you at dinner.
[car door opens, closes]
[engine turns over]
[car rumbles away]
[curious instrumentals]
[key scrapes and squeaks on car]
[keys rattle]
[clerk] Say hi to your wife for me.
Help you with something?
Um, yeah.
Do you sell any keys that look like this?
Now, that's a really cool one.
I think it's maybe...
17th century.
Do you mind?
Wow.
Well,
that's lighter than any iron I've felt.
Where did this come from?
[stammers] I'm not sure.
Well, let me see what I've got here.
[cabinet rattles]
[drawer thuds]
-[rustling in cabinet]
-[curious instrumentals]
[clerk] Hmm. [exhales]
[neck crinkles]
-Here.
-[jar of keys rattles]
These don't seem to be worth much
to anybody,
including me.
Go ahead, take 'em.
Thank you.
[shopping cart rattles]
[putty scraper clanks]
[ominous instrumentals]
-[Sam, sing-songy] Kinsey!
-[Nina breathes heavily]
-[screaming]
-[Sam] I was hoping
your dad would answer some questions,
-but he wasn't any help.
-[continued screaming]
[Sam] Will you help me, Kinsey?
[Sam] Last chance, Kinsey.
[Nina screams]
-[whack]
-[Sam thuds]
[hammers rattle]
[indistinct chatter]
[locker clanks open]
[locker door creaks]
[scoffs]
[echoing thuds]
[flips page]
[chuckles]
Hey.
How's it going?
Well, my brother left me high and dry
in a sea of strangers, so...
What are you, ten?
[door creaks, slams shut]
Look...
I'm sorry.
[indistinct yelling]
I'm just trying to make it through the day
without going crazy.
Seriously.
Yeah, me too.
Tyler?
[phone chimes]
-Hello!
-[phone chimes]
I'm sorry. Javi's waiting for me.
I should go.
[door creaks open]
Sorry, I'm a little early.
Oh, no worries.
Rufus is just out with the snowblower,
blowing us a back path.
-I'll go grab him.
-No, I can wait.
He doesn't like to leave
until everything's done.
Actually, I'm...
glad that we have some time.
There's something I want to ask you about.
You want some tea?
When I was talking to the English teacher,
Joe Ridgeway,
um, he made a reference to something,
some kind of... tragedy.
What was he talking about?
At the, uh...
the end of our senior year...
there was an accident.
Three of our friends drowned.
Oh, my God.
Where?
-[dramatic instrumentals]
-In the sea cave.
It's about a half mile north of here.
We had all just graduated and we were...
partying and...
not thinking about the tides.
I'm so sorry.
Why wouldn't Rendell have told me
about this?
Maybe he just didn't want to revisit it.
It was the most painful thing
that had ever happened to any of us.
I mean,
[stammers] I never talk about it myself.
Lucas...
[Ellie sighs]
I mean, I know most people think,
high school romances,
who cares? But...
he was something special.
[clinking]
[device knocks and thuds]
[sighs]
[heavy breathing]
[steady exhale]
[device cranking]
[suspenseful instrumentals]
-[device clanks shut]
-[gasps]
-[device slowly cranking]
-[struggles]
-[continued cranking]
-[grunts]
[exhales]
[metal scrapes and clicks]
[sighs in relief]
[exhales]
[rattling]
Let's put this key in it.
[suspenseful instrumentals crescendo
to silence]
[ominous instrumentals]
Stop with the drama, bro.
It's just a scratch.
-[Brinker scoffs]
-[door closes]
Hey, Logan.
What's up?
-[Logan] Something wrong?
-[Javi] Yeah.
Some garbage person keyed my car
for no reason.
[Logan] No shit!
Ah, that sucks.
-Have any idea who might have done it?
-[Javi] No.
[Javi] No one saw the piece of shit.
-[glass scrapes]
-[Logan clicks tongue]
-Tough break, man.
-[door closes]
[Brinker, hushed] Hey... Hey.
[sighs] I should get home.
My little brother is kinda--
Oh, no way, bro.
I'm mourning the loss of my paint job.
We need to drink.
-No, seriously--
-See you later, Logan.
[Tyler] What are you doing?
-[Tyler] Hey.
-Dude, it's fine. We do this all the time.
Bro, just tuck it under your arm
and follow our lead. Let's go.
[Brinker sighs]
[clerk] What do you think you're doing?
-[feet shuffling]
-[clerk grunts]
[door alarm rings]
-Are you okay?
-[grunts and sighs]
Look, I, um...
I don't even want this.
Can you please just...
take it back?
Not how it works, kid.
-Please, I just--
-[Logan] Hey.
I was wondering where you went.
I just went to the bathroom for a second,
which isn't the most accessible bathroom
I've ever been in.
Thanks for holding my beer for me, man.
[clerk] ID?
You even know this kid?
Yeah, that's Tyler Locke.
You heard of the Lockes, right?
They just moved into Key House.
Oh. Right. Yeah.
My condolences.
[Logan] Keep the change, man.
See you around, Tyler.
[door bell sounds]
[foreboding instrumentals]
[curious instrumentals]
[key opening crinkles]
[exhales steadily]
[rattling]
[door creaks open]
[carnival chatter]
Bode, hi.
-Did you miss me?
-[door closes]
I had a really wonderful day
because of you.
It was so fun.
I even won you--
My gosh.
[dubious instrumentals]
What...
did you find?
[trap snaps shut]
Bode.
Did you think you could trap me
and then make me give you back the key?
I thought we were friends.
We're not friends.
You lied to me
and you tried to kill my mom.
What other keys have you found?
I haven't found any more.
[hushed] Well...
maybe you need to try harder
and when you find them,
you're going to give them back to me.
-[yelling] And why would I do that?
-[sharp inhale]
Because when I come back,
-I'm not going to be so nice.
-[struggling]
[Bode gasps and struggles]
[Bode gasps, then pants]
-[coughing and gasping]
-Happy hunting, Bode.
-[key rattles in lock]
-[Bode grunts]
-[door creaks open]
-[wind whirs]
[Bode gasps for air]
[coughs]
Duct tape.
[dog barks in the distance]
Thanks.
[duct tape tears]
[beaded curtains rattle]
What's up? I'm Gabe.
Craft service?
[Scot] Oh, yeah, sorry.
Gabe is new to Matheson, too.
Yeah, we were on a frantic search
for our monster
so we offered him friendship in exchange
for wearing a suit that doesn't breathe.
-[Scot laughs]
-It does not smell awesome in here.
So, what exactly are you?
Wait, you mean
you've never heard of Amphropeta?
-It's like a local legend.
-[Scot] Half man,
half lobster, fully ticked off about
how we persecute his brethren
in the deep. [laughs]
Every now and then
he'll snatch up a fisherman or a whaler.
Or teenagers dry humping
on the beach.
He's probably untethered the soul
of one of your ancestors
with a mighty...
-[claw clomps]
-snap of the claw.
Sorry.
I forgive you.
Practical effects will be mental.
Zadie's been working on this application
for weeks.
When Gabe attacks,
I'm gonna make the head pop off
into the air
and the blood's going to spurt up
this tube and all over Eden.
[Eden laughs] Okay, sorry wait.
I didn't think
I was gonna get blood all over me.
[all together] It's in the script.
[pages rustle]
"Blood erupts from Nathaniel's neck
like a geyser and rains down
in a grisly torrent
on Amanda as she screams."
But I didn't think you were actually going
to drown me in blood.
[Zadie] It's corn syrup and food coloring.
It's fully edible and washable.
But I don't understand
why we can't just do it without the blood.
Because we got the couch from Goodwill
and you're aware, Eden,
that the title of the movie is
The Splattering.
Well, then it's me or the blood.
Blood. I vote blood.
I mean, obviously.
[dog barks in the distance]
[stammers] Oh, I get a vote?
Um...
[stammers] Yeah, I'll say blood, too.
The ayes have it, Eden.
I'm out of here.
Bye. Love you.
[Eden] Well, you guys just destroyed
your own film.
[beaded curtains clink]
[door opens]
[door slams]
-[Scot sighs]
-So what now?
Well, I don't know, Doug. Pitch me a fix.
Well,
maybe Kinsey could do it.
[Scot stammers] Oh, no, no...
I don't think that's a good idea.
Um... [stammering]
I don't think Kinsey's wheelhouse
is in line with this
particular brand of cinematic methodology.
No, I can do it.
Really? Y-Yeah?
Yeah, sure. [inhales]
But I was told
there would be smoothies. [sighs]
[Scot laughs]
-So, you are Amanda
-[smoke puffing]
and you just started in the early stages
of your new relationship with Nathaniel,
who in the other scenes
will be played by yours truly.
Wow, you're an actor, too?
-I mean...
-Actor is a stretch.
Douglas, please with the chit chat.
I'm working with my lead.
Anyway,
so... you're about to sit down
and watch a movie
and perhaps let things progress
-[slurping]
-to the next proverbial base.
You're excited, but you're nervous.
You're full of desire,
but you've got a complicated past.
Make sense?
-I think so.
-Great.
[Zadie] And just so you know,
we really only have one shot at this,
so...
[Scot] Okay, let's go. And...
[stomps] places, people! Places!
-[switch clicks]
-[Scot] And roll sound, Doug.
Sound is sounding.
-[camera trills]
-Zadie, slate.
[Zadie] The Splattering, scene 23,
-take one.
-[slate claps]
Mark.
[Scot] It's go time.
And... action.
Nathaniel. [scoffs]
I can't believe you started the movie
without me.
I hope I didn't put too much butter
on the popcorn.
No such thing.
[Kinsey stifles laugh]
And, Gabe.
-[hollow knock]
-[curtains rattle]
[Gabe roars indistinctly]
-[dubious instrumentals]
-Okay. In three...
two... one!
[spurting]
[Kinsey pants]
Okay, now, now Kinsey, scream.
-[splattering]
-[Sam, echoed and sing-songy] Kinsey...
[Scot] Kinsey,
Kinsey, scream.
-[whacks plastic]
-[Sam] Kinsey...
[Scot] Kinsey,
[laughs] do something.
-[Scot] Kinsey!
-[KInsey pants]
[Scot] Cut. Cut. Cut.
-[Doug] Cutting.
-[Scot sighs]
[dog barking in distance]
I'm sorry.
Hey, well, no, hey, it's... [chuckles]
it's all right.
It's okay. It's, um...
Don't worry about it.
This... this blood is too red.
We're going to have to reshoot anyway,
so it's... Right, guys?
Yeah. Maybe we can fix it in post.
Doug Prazila,
you did not just say that to me.
[Kinsey exhales]
-[light tapping on plate]
-Thanks for your help today.
Sorry Kinsey and Tyler couldn't make it
to dinner.
Oh, don't sweat it.
They're teenagering.
It just means more moo shu pork
for us, right?
[Nina chuckles]
Duncan...
why do you think Rendell
never told me about that drowning?
What drowning?
Rendell's friends. His best friend, Lucas.
Right, yeah... Um...
I must not have...
I don't really remember.
What are you talking about?
[stammers] You lived here
when it happened.
It must have been totally traumatic.
Yeah, it probably was for Rendell.
But... you're his brother
and they were his closest friends and...
they died.
I don't understand
how you wouldn't remember that.
Look... Rendell was a lot older than me.
He and his friends,
they mostly kept to themselves.
So they probably just...
[chopsticks tap plate]
Honestly, I don't know
why I don't remember.
It's like that whole time period
is just...
rubbed out.
[ominous instrumentals]
I don't really understand it.
[sighs, then laughs]
It's probably why I don't like
spending a lot of time down here.
Did Rendell ever mention Sam Lesser
to you?
-[door opens]
-No, why?
[door closes]
[Duncan] Hey!
Kinsey, just in time.
Well, the chow mein's kicked,
but there's still some spring rolls.
Jesus!
-[Nina] What the hell happened?
-It's fine. It's fake blood.
Edible and washable.
I'm going to clean up.
[Kinsey sniffles]
[steady exhale]
[solemn instrumentals]
I got you a present.
You didn't have to get me anything.
You only graduate middle school once...
if you're doing it right.
[Kinsey exhales in awe]
-This is so cool.
-[chuckles]
I've been holding on to that
for a long time.
I think...
you're old enough to wear it now.
[takes a deep breath]
It's kind of a family heirloom.
[Kinsey] Thanks, Dad.
-I love it.
-[chuckles]
It's always been special to me.
I know you'll take good care of it.
You never talk about your family.
[laughs] We just...
We just went in different directions.
Now you guys are all the family I need.
You're so much more than I ever deserved.
Just stick together,
you and your brothers.
Yeah.
Hey.
I'm so proud of you.
[solemn instrumentals continue]
[cries]
[catches breath]
[sobs]
[curious instrumentals]
[neck opening crinkles]
[light crunching and squishing]
[radar effect]
[suspenseful instrumentals]
[lid rattles and creaks open]
[technological chatter and whirring]
Wow...
I covered for you with Mom.
Said you were in the school library,
studying.
Thanks.
Yeah, you're welcome.
What do you want from me, Kinsey?
I'd be an idiot to want anything
from you, Tyler,
especially when you're in this state.
Don't tell me about my state, okay?
-Just... I'm tired.
-You used to talk to me,
about everything,
about nothing. But now that I...
Now that real shit's going on...
I don't even recognize you anymore.
It's starting to scare me.
I'm the same as I always was.
No, you're not. You're...
[suspenseful instrumentals]
Bode?
Bode!
-[lid creaks open]
-Hey, guys! You gotta come see this!
[arcade chatter]
Follow me!
["Big Love" by She Wants Revenge plays]
What the--
♪ Get your big love on,
Get your big love ♪
[lively instrumentals]